<root>
<kyero>
<feed_version>2</feed_version>
</kyero>
<property>
<id>16430407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 15:09:53</date>
<ref>AP1-DL-T001042</ref>
<price>70000</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Apartment</en>
</type>
<town>Torrevieja</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>La Mata</location_detail>
<beds>1</beds>
<baths>1</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
Rare offer Just 50 meters away from the sandy La Mata Beach next to Cabo Cervera. Beach front apartment in a nice residence in a wonderful location with all you may need close at hand. Nice beaches, all local amenities, lots of restaurants, and connected by the city bus lines to all other parts of Torrevieja, the marina, all kinds of water sports and large shopping centres. This property has the potential to earn a good rental income. Appointments at any time.
</en>
<de>
Einzigartiges Angebot nur 50 Meter vom Sandstrand entfernt in Cabo Cervera in La Mata: Strandapartment in einer schönen Residenz in wunderschöner Lage mit allem, was Sie in der Nachbarschaft brauchen. Schöne Strände, alle lokalen Annehmlichkeiten, viele Restaurants und Stadtbusse, die mit allen anderen Teilen von Torrevieja, der Marina, allen Arten von Wassersportarten und großen Einkaufszentren verbunden sind. Diese Wohnung bietet Ihnen auch gute Mieteinnahmen bei der Vermietung. Vereinbaren Sie Termine zu jeder Zeit.
</de>
<fr>
Offre unique à seulement 50 mètres de la plage de sable à côté de Cabo Cervera à La Mata: Appartement de plage dans une belle résidence à un bel endroit avec tout ce dont vous avez besoin dans le quartier. Belles plages, toutes les commodités locales, de nombreux restaurants et bus de la ville reliés à toutes les autres parties de Torrevieja, la marina, toutes sortes de sports nautiques et de grands centres commerciaux. Cet appartement vous donne également un bon revenu locatif lors de la location. Organisez un rendez-vous à tout moment.
</fr>
<nl>
Uniek aanbod op slechts 50 meter van het zandstrand naast Cabo Cervera in La Mata: Strandappartement in een mooie residentie op een prachtige locatie met alles wat u nodig heeft in de buurt. Mooie stranden, alle lokale voorzieningen, veel restaurants en door stadsbuslijnen verbonden met alle andere delen van Torrevieja, de jachthaven, allerlei watersporten en grote winkelcentra. Dit appartement geeft u bij verhuur ook goede huurinkomsten. Afspraken voor bezichtiging op elk moment te regelen.
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/wyHa_810IawfR1yBgBwLxYveAcdC5gqxD1KS2A4NF0ajdqNITa0lG2U5vFexRiloLUa9OLoI5G5DZq68=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1J_FbW28YEyvoiBlCK1Jvf6cxQEGg81jkBzS29TIojkqB9G73Js1HJR_5th851yaOhDHQvh4v96IBfFZxw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/uoZyMKSQY5y1JsGQ5Jh32Rdx5nHdhBv7gF36b80tLLfP9ZxDm19irlJlfp07Bfomx5lBd4UnWFRH9Ke06Q=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/yT0AJCjS6rUFN6RadnkhLf8WLeYGzK08jAti_IZy0ZKRmPsjih7JOECbC1kSwcBahfcIbY5Wt_ZHAyIJ4w=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/omVT9l-h8gpy1pVrsD11V41P2eh1rjH8-jg6zqjrHSdXptzv_IkRf4IKEZNEEaglGKDsLlV6r6Yhb-Vi=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/3wrr2JbIihJ2j7Gn8vENLb2yKt6qNzNaUMHzj0p-0z6AOfZD3dy67BGSzPft8kRpouAX9i9t338tW6Bx1hA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1Of2HAafJtZo4PATSXvzAqBWkUpzZXfh-IrkRkMbN5W5jIWFCkUkKwdZhsqLpz8j6EtmFLukx7UAvVw0Ajw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/sfLCGyPu8fWuUaiE3Kq5F-OjLB2fCCcJa88B-jqcIBNHheo2oX79GXbXRk0Cte6sJV2S0E7zk3xlG5he2w=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/J7L7X3a_HIagT5gJIV9BgPVk03Mk__TH_kDsKUw8JjTKlSa58hEPO57CIOtfRyZv0A1fLuKIN2qHodR6Mw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/MyHxwzDUQRacEXAZQVexeg_wheq4NfUPofs-33MOreYtxTk_kfb7TfpwoQMUKZ2z1Tq3rdaXAvlosrDqYOQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/HpaAve3RWr4TP2sHRv9YDunspb5SYTKr2i_-bNakzEBy12wjmXparJ8YO8iR4Dyp24I1Bkl-_AMVNf-6=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/4rvg3bYF3bzu8Y01n9py0AiMJfH9HRco_WzwjhqTit2h0EIJ-qThBO7P2hwIkaGPYHeqlCjCiEw0iJgSCQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2c6vSTofEMzS0jkEtxiYdOJoNSgTufIVux5FuoUWgvNWMm0KNqmprjZA9Tosm3zwWxpPW_gzVd9N1iD0=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/UQ5VYNNrQbf-RtG2EiIDiCYXPOJWhkT02QO2BkiyjS89tGkGeM4wNXyEFHTjpPrteIlcmK-tMhF3kKAFrg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Q5UKJVY5Lo9OyPzTDCcvYONA_XJB_RW1Or6Ci3x_Wf0zTLGkXpKWobC-OFu3U2dQ3CdiQTyU5aprDeov=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/GCijcmkXp1gSO8b_7Wy5k_hQ_iF1nUDXxp0K7JVCWuZY07ZhLFjZqZ1YcxfqVK4P3gk5qboc8RuyxWp9=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="17">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/uOvRAkMPEJiaHmd_kJrjMTnZCK1oORvthaGkUErTkIaAZPFxRDjcj06YNsqqLJO6ZkFB3yhW-QITOzjH8A=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="18">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/lmOMvQEhxp-JHIoy3utQ1qdFaS_OkHKK4ttWx25h2leZBLwngq21wuJ1948NPCU2NdFsMS-92Q3-i2R8=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="19">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Gz4SrsgvjbfkvMAgQ5-Lr66XOuSEur6pnFQzxUPpoBqSVSDpoNI5Bz7SKkQNCiM3wc2664jALE0ChHGjoA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="20">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/4jQareuZ_TIExAJC70HdWERoIWrxFZdJFYHFOXTZj-KM1I-7aLXpA_DszHSBcIBbJdJLSTXnGZ9oHbsNqQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="21">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/r2GK8z8bsixoAnZLgJYeXRxprXeWgTXSGdghfwDbA-rHXV7xq9nm13RUDjIcVzSod9Puoilmhzew3L0pag=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="22">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/MsPNDqVe7-SrlMbBEpqZv4jzgsLxwqR8huzeAKupl5xp5aGpcn_FDEDOlAGXVj1JnF_bUiG4Mi8CeLY2ZA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>17720407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 15:07:55</date>
<ref>AP1-DL-Z007584</ref>
<price>79950</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Apartment</en>
</type>
<town>Orihuela Costa</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>La Zenia</location_detail>
<beds>1</beds>
<baths>1</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
This beautiful south facing apartment with seaview from the large balcony is really worth your money! Located in La Zenia, one of the most sought after areas in the Costa Blanca, just a short walk away from off course La Zenia Beach and the famous Zenia Boulevard, all kind of bars, restaurants, supermarkets, 4 international golf courses and much, much more! This sunny apartment is recently renovated, fully furnished and comes with a private parking spot. Don't feel like going to the beach? Just jump in the large communal pool and relax in the sun on the lush green grass! Come and book your personal viewing now with the Maxgoldhouse team.
</en>
<de>
Diese schöne Wohnung in Südlage mit Meerblick vom großen Balkonaus ist wirklich Ihr Geld wert! Die Residenz liegt in La Zenia, einer der begehrtesten Gegenden an der Costa Blanca, nur wenige Gehminuten vom Strand La Zenia und dem berühmten Zenia Boulevard entfernt. Alle Arten von Bars, Restaurants, Supermärkte, 4 internationale Golfplätze und vieles mehr, viel mehr - ist hier Standard ! Diese sonnige Wohnung wurde kürzlich renoviert, ist komplett möbliert und verfügt über einen privaten Parkplatz. Lust nicht zum Strand zu gehen? Springen Sie einfach in den großen Gemeinschaftspool und entspannen Sie in der Sonne auf dem grünen Gras! Kommen Sie und buchen Sie Ihre persönliche Besichtigung jetzt mit dem Maxgoldhouse-Team.
</de>
<fr>
Ce bel appartement orienté plein sud avec vue sur la mer depuis le grand balcon vaut vraiment le coup! Situé à La Zenia, l'une des zones les plus populaires de la Costa Blanca, à quelques pas de La Zenia Beach et du célèbre Zenia Boulevard, de toutes sortes de bars, restaurants, supermarchés, 4 terrains de golf internationaux et bien plus encore! Cet appartement ensoleillé a été récemment rénové, est entièrement meublé et dispose d'un parking privé. Tu n'as pas envie d'aller à la plage? Juste sautez dans la grande piscine communale et se détendez au soleil sur l'herbe verte luxuriante! Venez réserver votre visite personnelle avec l'équipe de Maxgoldhouse.
</fr>
<nl>
Dit mooie appartement op het zuiden met zeezicht vanaf het grote balkon is echt uw geld waard! Gelegen in La Zenia, één van de meest populaire gebieden in de Costa Blanca, op slechts een korte loopafstand van La Zenia Beach en de beroemde Zenia Boulevard, allerlei bars, restaurants, supermarkten, 4 internationale golfbanen en nog veel, veel meer! Dit zonnige appartement is onlangs gerenoveerd, volledig ingericht en heeft een eigen parkeerplaats. Heb je geen zin om naar het strand te gaan? Spring gewoon in het grote gemeenschappelijke zwembad en ontspan in de zon op het weelderige, groene gras! Kom en boek nu uw persoonlijke bezichtiging met het Maxgoldhouse-team.
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/UcAVuHDwwNJfPk6nLfRb8I_5TLmftWf4J7tU5pxnB5kFulYoP5WSmWPweauH1pREXxGFOIQuO9x80Bqq5A=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2akQZAFXkZdyP3UrSOktWXKoWZJwzk8chacPtnWDIUFjtzmLINghQUAnYbhQz1NFaD0kqPuVIyTtwEiP0kw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/eck0t8YWbro1YmNsbnpq6A-nVd0415HL0RlU_Ygmjg4-ysvqMf6rcPFYU2utn1dR5sBL5e8nmLT70O10qQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/_n_aUKymNsjDWYjFadYzN5PCWiVgtAfrIMscNLfVVoHLU13uPmpd-d0I4F5iIaFZ6b4A2J6ZH8nk7eWbNBE=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1li-Mc7P9_CzTry4DHdBhWTjNY337N8_JT4DrjJWJ8pAFumw-SN1UV_CeLU0yNyB9eZvlmoeUkZ3y2oykew=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/L5FpBgEJKnCQMHygHNQ8-PDgbAAkUpC8yutqYe36JB-H9LHXirfFxbNMmsahVtpLCRXfnx1Gd7GofWPt=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/hvhkQbBZmR_9RRdig1URZrHNU-Ta7Wws9zTIC4RmqJOMOF2Ylgpy7dyuqJ_OMktYQ_x8trta916ApHL9XwM=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/d3AQvUJwlBFPkbTBmd8E-W_H16C5ACPc42yK_sLgkjTZgtvC6yQYUsDdG5YT1vhbtGMw3lzYs97mH7jLlQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/79Hcst1tR8DDzyzvznIynnTBDi5EqV1u7jR2KUu4eUyawDHZ4TGNuZx9YPdu_QBW8GDYHcfc7KxX69iI=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/pJprGgRxymulr4mOWwulIrYBHnoWZVqgvF-DIVlM2eQd9M43_9m79BHFumLQ7czABmQY5QB6z1bAtiRa2Q=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Jfr9RfIEM5w5-zjW0rUTzjIDLeYuhCcCNBYEmo6wAG0Pjrs9G08ojTAhXIYAtM9Go-m_E45uEwMhHYn0wg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/sNeRKcidNnSjiWbios8aJhMhlWhAaLI7zU4h6dr9H1MiYblEEblgG3B2cfGHFKcdZZqWd2kOyT8I7EPM1g=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/uat5CXw2fWS1Q6frbE4Sa8D6KoLzs1D7Eh7zvbtzZUx4x9S4tUa2LWUx_d97O8X0zz58VEty8XtSPhOyEtE=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/WKcnWHunPmSwxJb2vTgf223l7ACh-bOPXUg2m6RMyiUBga-_ZUhz4X7Iu7OKP2Z38A5Ba89wCjQAnu8Wfw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/eOHLDSJ29onE9NWojVZ5UTXVWODJ-98AzwPlesr4lxRwFq4RCkh8BVs38lj5w1ftC2lZv941dYxsw0BjewM=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/871bLJId5mlBIzbg6zyoX_kAkWab9JzM3eCELtGWAloJOjUQ1IZbQdn3LXI7Y5RQIG9xkwOrE7YhHiqYwsE=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="17">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/HNYBHt4E1OIvJHVzx8LyiPJoUABmMUZ0OtcThkimaDIT0QNEN_Ha0CQWg-ClOta2H1o_9JyBBDHaWTB-=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="18">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/IEfvT1rwXiynW203zG0Oo-y4D9sCCqlUjRp4YRPSD8XhOjQilD5uCBXuUavXG184eEX0aUECO7ovv2Hw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>63505699062109342410407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 12:53:52</date>
<ref>AP2-DL-C00072</ref>
<price>85000</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Apartment</en>
</type>
<town>Orihuela Costa</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>Cabo Roig</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>1</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
Cabo Roig: Looking for an investment with appreciation, or a place in the SUN. We offer the highest quality of life - beach, sea, many miles of walking, golf, etc. - this property in the Cabo Roig / Orihuela Costa area offers pure Spanish style living. Some golf courses are just minutes away and also the picturesque harbour and the lovely cafes and restaurants and not to forget the daily shopping! It takes very little time.This property is located just a short walk from local bars, shops, restaurant, supermarket and the local bus stop. The golden beaches of Campoamor and Cabo Roig are just a few minutes drive away as are 4 golf courses. Alicante airport is 45 minutes drive and Murcia San Javier airport is 20 minutes drive away. We look forward to your showing you this property.
</en>
<de>
Schön gelegene Wohnung in gepflegter Residenz nahe zum Meer - im Bereich Lomas de Cabo Roig. In guter Anbindung zu allem was man so braucht - incl Sandstrände, Jachthafen, Wassersport, Golfplätze - Shopping Zentren und mehr. Ein guter Ort für Urlaub und zum Überwintern. Die Residenz hat eine grosse Poolanlage und ist in excellentem Zustand.
</de>
<fr>
Cabo Roig: Vous cherchez un investissement rentable, ou une place au soleil? Nous vous offrons le meilleur de la vie: plage, mer, se promener, golf, etc. Cet appartement à Cabo Roig, Orihuela Costa, vous garantit la vie espagnole pure. Plusieurs terrains de golf sont à quelques minutes en voiture, tout comme le port pittoresque, la plage, des cafés agréables et des restaurants. Pour les achats quotidiens, vous pouvez aller ici. L'aéroport d'Alicante est à 45 minutes et l'aéroport de Murcia (San Javier) à seulement 20 minutes. Nous voudrions vous montrer cet appartement.
</fr>
<nl>
Cabo Roig: Op zoek naar een waardevolle investering, of een plaats in de zon? Wij bieden u het beste van het leven: strand, zee, wandelen, golfen, etc. Dit appartement in Cabo Roig, Orihuela Costa, staat garant voor het pure Spaanse leven. Een aantal golfbanen zijn op slechts enkele minuten rijden, net als de pittoreske haven, het strand, gezellige cafés en restaurants. Ook voor de dagelijkse boodschappen kan je hier terecht. De luchthaven van Alicante ligt op 45 minuten rijden en de luchthaven van Murcia (San Javier) op 20 minuten. Wij verheugen er ons u dit appartement te laten zien.
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-eS7ZQcbctPE/WCHBrk-5qCI/AAAAAAAAOGY/acaI40dJBFw1cLTfgMIDVI_zNcEXdYyjQCHM/s640/1a.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-w8pnLzCmXgI/WCHBrkF5ZUI/AAAAAAAAOGY/WK33D2r7W2gRnSXCgraILolUdtZhwocOQCHM/s640/1b.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-kXrgAm2PT2A/WCHBrurbfRI/AAAAAAAAOGY/scO3soe6YpA6A06DG3Gbyq9-7o0r37vOgCHM/s640/1ccc.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-nN4673NIH9Y/WCHBrn-BFKI/AAAAAAAAOGY/VR77L6ztsm8nfgSqy9jdst11VF8dk4YcQCHM/s640/1d.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Nbxk3yTlnZ0/WCHBrio2NpI/AAAAAAAAOGY/zQ2eHGrZCh4C6z2hGwEVLPODb0vCn1oeACHM/s640/2a.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-YlhNkw4_vac/WCHBrg5VIOI/AAAAAAAAOGY/90IxYYwuaDMx6O_r1KWQljqq_D8B-GpuwCHM/s640/2b.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-JRf-T5CxxTc/WCHBrniLXHI/AAAAAAAAOGY/ks8aUgHO7BU80sP0YRYriHMHBOXAWhP_ACHM/s640/2c.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-H1DTZWDIGOQ/WCHBruisNfI/AAAAAAAAOGY/JaOfAo0xuE8U08FwwMv8S8My6qHdrlYlgCHM/s640/2d.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-9jsAi5tWttM/WCHBrtivlrI/AAAAAAAAOGY/Z5V9yFBa__EAiiCntucvv0X0nMJdGRrhACHM/s640/3a.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-SrnmOtqjJoE/WCHBrs5kqDI/AAAAAAAAOGY/tcIu1VCh0X4jqZ6t14EU1vmf8-9HpSRkACHM/s640/3b.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-gi_P9LK7JL8/WCHBrnQHS6I/AAAAAAAAOGY/deo7dWvr3SASb6W4XW0RlENKSp9WlSeWACHM/s640/4.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-SGifnGAFyV8/WCHBriEOSXI/AAAAAAAAOGY/gC2fsEyZFSw9s6EtoC6Afn8OanAeyqTPACHM/s640/5.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-avoSXn-8YuI/WCHBrgBn7TI/AAAAAAAAOGY/6YvF_B2e2yUBN88m6h6QapmKUMfwgwiEQCHM/s640/6.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-k3FT6AzHMOI/WCHBrpX7l5I/AAAAAAAAOGY/o2xEPKfAGhI0Z--Id8TlO08RSe2NOmw8QCHM/s640/7.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>16670407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 13:45:56</date>
<ref>AP2-DL-PF00420</ref>
<price>88000</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Apartment</en>
</type>
<town>Orihuela Costa</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>Playa Flamenca</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>1</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
This lovely top floor duplex bungalow in the peaceful, well kept Miramar residence of Playa Flamenca offers you the perfect holiday spot! This property is in excellent condition and the rooftop extension offers an additional room. Within a short walk of all needed amenities in Playa Flamenca and within a short drive the beaches are plentiful and vary from vast expanses of sand to small pebble coves. Many of the safe white sandy beaches are proud to display the prestigious Blue Flag, which is awarded by the EU for cleanliness and safety. Playa Flamenca is also close to 5 international golf courses, large shopping centres and has its own huge saturday mercadillo / market. This is a MUST for your saturday morning.
</en>
<de>
Diese wunderschöne Maisonette-Wohnung im Obergeschoss in der ruhigen, gepflegten Residenz Miramar in Playa Flamenca bietet Ihnen den perfekten Urlaubsort! Diese Wohnung ist in einem ausgezeichneten Zustand und die Erweiterung auf dem Dach bietet ein zusätzliches Zimmer. Ein kurzer Spaziergang von allen notwendigen Annehmlichkeiten in Playa Flamenca und mit einer kurzen Autofahrt gibt es viele Strände, von ausgedehnten Sandstränden bis hin zu kleinen Kiesbuchten. Viele der sicheren, weißen Sandstrände sind stolz auf ihre prestigeträchtige Blaue Flagge, die von der EU für Sauberkeit und Sicherheit verliehen wird. Playa Flamenca ist auch in der Nähe von 5 internationalen Golfplätzen, großen Einkaufszentren und hat seinen eigenen großen Mercadillo / Markt am Samstag: Ein sehr angenehmer Start in Ihren Samstagmorgen.
</de>
<fr>
Ce bel appartement duplex à l'étage supérieur dans la résidence calme et bien entretenu Miramar à Playa Flamenca vous offre le lieu de vacances idéal! Cet appartement est en excellent état et l'agrandissement sur le toit vous offre une pièce supplémentaire. Une courte promenade de toutes les commodités nécessaires à Playa Flamenca et à une courte distance en voiture il y a de nombreuses plages, allant de grandes plages de sable à petites baies de galets. La plupart des plages de sable blanc sécurisées sont fières de leur prestigieux drapeau bleu, décerné par l'UE pour la propreté et la sécurité. Playa Flamenca est également proche de 5 terrains de golf internationaux, de grands centres commerciaux et a son propre grand Mercadillo / marché le samedi: Un début très agréable pour votre samedi matin.
</fr>
<nl>
Dit mooie duplex appartement op de bovenverdieping in de rustige, goed onderhouden residentie Miramar in Playa Flamenca biedt u de perfecte vakantieplek! Dit appartement is in uitstekende staat en de uitbouw op het dak biedt een extra kamer. Op korte loopafstand van alle benodigde voorzieningen in Playa Flamenca en met een korte autorit zijn er de vele stranden, variërend van uitgestrekte zandstranden tot kleine kiezelbaaien. Veel van de veilige, witte zandstranden zijn trots op hun prestigieuze Blauwe Vlag, die door de EU wordt toegekend voor properheid en veiligheid. Playa Flamenca ligt ook dichtbij 5 internationale golfbanen, grote winkelcentra en heeft zijn eigen grote mercadillo / markt op zaterdag: Een heel aangenaam begin van uw zaterdagochtend.
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/hTlEa1Qsq9Ahz7GgfK0XYN4DQBo9-ATxnzgCEXXLMJAlZAjUvplnYhKGkG6Sjws0P1YJyFs-qBq3F3gxNQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/k6_kvv-ZKosaWCMHp-yRfTJsy3B5FCf2VgkNhkNWjOcLu6pwbiKM4cDX8lpOY_GByDoIgMcnXlmNoi2IPoE=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/MrCOYKnqn1qGqXd1NFT5JRxXH0m8t6EMsWZPKXA5qmZeFyUShboyVjE5ZlGOTNAgcVRuywg9itXhu6MyuQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/aQ3nhqPe3ynWWLDepfxW4NsDCR6MG4i8TMwnqZEnik9cAqXtDizvLnqzaGl-AABoHwnViLqioaoDnJzB=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/9FXCTH5HZ3xuP6YnysEF-91mRYGdhmQ7PBTk3rKk64ku6-UAI6WZZ2lXVowns6bPP6rKKgYdb5ytX1igUyQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ceO0tvCDamXfuPH5QX247trkFf4Gu4ILPsPI5-MMOwL8Bh7jegiEWNsl3HmoMUYzvCTZkGg1ZUA4uxjp=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/J2RkUh4YLI01lwTOwbVk78zsuqC5Iy5GHFFch0frov7W-_wb0I9c-hMAxGg37VdX-jMN5360viotijlTlQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/elSEOh6pHsyUTO7yPvxkQnZZvKUbJpsMTQqw4b3_oR-7OtzNrcXtQ2Z3l4q3DgVDpSKoALiKLUPuVCZEmL8=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/gFCuOPQEXmfG0ukOuVEDT5EYfUYbsqcDoyoc7lGxCKbLB9VAldmwQ6cYCPixi8DajSVEbgPhZ3JiXjZ0Bkg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/5wmVMqliQTmHnrUSZFxk4d_doeftPcWlPZ_IVaFOjBRDeOufsixsW4a4cuZ2vWPigokpwawtvFVrnypK2A=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/tkxT7mDEXT6TfqLDHlnijidnovLzNQLcTLTTa1eMKj5hZI9i-dJbXm0w2DjtglY3hKnJTjPjyXFQqqdd=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/51X_ZO_8iBfM_BaEdQexw1NGrxWF7LSUFcMYML2XnOlr5hU-u0QrTXbHFGhGLnzQVNyp48Z-dWjHJsfILA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Xnnbizblr_Z8trw9uMI0p95JO2BOmcGbW3dpuibuRGSfa_PjjlKsIarBMAtE6wFSUF2PlrkvDWvG4MgaoE0=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/H1uNMdZ5wqb_xp6Sfd8ZnO6lqdAiLdOCug6QHWFRJtMO-nb_GZMpXPO9e3CKRVZIQ6J2YFJ5ajI4elwtsEk=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/5cFmFXi8dSqZ9HkBGuQSm7Jh7EFfHZ_DC5eeiS5dNu53nA-TGrDcurmHXSi2wYSZOy105eeIU03WGk7RKA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ThDJCkw4yLLvSQRkLTcp7t8GujTRdlRVlRwyA1gXBSvCmtyfWSTex0PLgBLJZiS_Rn1ytwQDMcFmQ8Cvdg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="17">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/nCR9fbwm5qdRZG6k62o-Ioxugyx0OO9yypTlofA5UNiVo_BAQxX5721dYPS0KzFElamXdYLxJi9qpQI5qg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="18">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/EPYMOWcdzBEsUTsUWnjYDHyB4dF5Co2ZqnfGm8vne39fRUcw-9U0jQuVI_mUV8DiQ_rW_qPyb1Jvd0t8Qg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="19">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/zj3Icu_lqrWNnxFlqwjVaord2wEAoavPEok6Hk2c_37S2YX0AIBQ2TdNp89KuXnn7cDtPmqxclBTXHzP=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="20">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/wD8dB7JXHWiYEZrsoIEuGTRUNags93ySAStGm46f8chAWpMOr_nfM8xwrAgb9BB4nbwtms1cvfKjnf7zifU=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="21">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/atzyr7GbU7gjPZIjB_hbNHjS00tCLaBNMSn5pkmgWDuOa48T6_Ijhfw_I4YneSdDilwZc3OiQ7f3fd5nqg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="22">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/EZhTeqV-t4MO_AS9dnImidm7qJf_gPlnHBmXLnOrCZ3Nsogj9iJqYJ1Wdr343lWCSjkMzPSitb87FYtC=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="23">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dVlSKs-T8heKpQ1d21VT1S8SE76Rh4v6ka-D0wubT_1kmX4lSlJXtnkoqH_WSFsFVWBQpS_KMdywmXOq3g=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="24">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/X8gdV8AXpeC29tu-seqziMP11YKlvq7bZwbJU-NAGtsFwtm9U5p4IM93F9HOOwe7Rrl0aE5g6FBUlRhq7w=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="25">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/vRzg_7tmgeyAOO9V6hW_EcSThBhETgq64nBrzMGM3CsL0N8DMCpW78Awimp5KyPfxLFyOKWiol7woqvZAg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="26">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/IFDv2QmHIqB9H820tQs-vhbFEYdjJiG971KtcVIbT0yh9LFwrI4CiqIUpucL8qe76teQTyxX3DGwJ3ydEA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>18190407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 10:55:01</date>
<ref>AP2-DL-TPA8070</ref>
<price>89000</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Apartment</en>
</type>
<town>Torrevieja</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>Los Balcones</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>1</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
This 2 bedroom 1 bathroom top floor apartment in Los Balcones benefits from beautiful garden areas, a fantastic communal pool and a tennis court. The property has an open living/dining area, a fully equipped kitchen and comes fully furnished. Los Balcones is located in the Torrevieja area close to the beach and the marina and a wide selection of bars and restaurants. A selection of golf courses and the popular Zenia Boulevard are a short drive away. Contact Maxgoldhouse today for a viewing!!
</en>
<de>DE</de>
<fr>
Cet appartement au dernier étage à Los Balcones avec 2 chambres et 1 salle de bain a de beaux jardins, une fantastique piscine commune et un court de tennis. La propriété dispose d'un salon / salle à manger décloisonné, d'une cuisine entièrement équipée et est entièrement meublée. Los Balcones est situé à Torrevieja, à proximité de la plage et du port de plaisance et d'un large choix de bars et de restaurants. Aussi les terrains de golf et le populaire Zenia Boulevard sont seulement une courte distance en voiture. Contactez Maxgoldhouse aujourd'hui pour une visite!
</fr>
<nl>
Dit appartement op de bovenste verdieping in Los Balcones met 2 slaapkamer en 1 badkamer heeft prachtige tuinen, een fantastisch gemeenschappelijk zwembad en een tennisbaan. De accommodatie heeft een open woon- / eetkamer, een volledig uitgeruste keuken en is volledig gemeubeld. Los Balcones ligt in Torrevieja, dicht bij het strand en de jachthaven en een brede selectie aan bars en restaurants. Ook de golfbanen en het populaire Zenia Boulevard zijn maar een klein eindje rijden. Neem vandaag nog contact op met Maxgoldhouse voor een bezichtiging !!
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/45eGtiy6S5_Hyyb36NnubxdYh4bHHlyHgeApUQq6YKHltPMPsfRXNDr_V57dpBqwJ2PKDDUCMRCtxmeuiQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/aXCo5tt-6GKo_xV4XCPtizsjj2o1Fg9jh9Xgu8jcNQUp5WBQCqC4gQtugMsKcp_64-5f8R5uUWU-DOzbaAI=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/s2xVNyuCuzyMlbomq1oNhZ-oS4Av32C-SphvDhUBE4Ddo0y0j3eg2OLKHqvf91W8o2K0s8gkJus6aM0H9g=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/RbHLETsPIKbh2m6jfok84224EMpi1OogMiegupTfdj1HXeONxTS6vPwBA5Dqiio3ZAdcQIL3X4PKzRLcUQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/MqdylTFWIWpbHd9ySyhR9hBJW9ghWo_M-G8CzodUT9sYpeEnefihbjH8EqTeIZyE2RQD3v9Hef_-I5KzVg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/5dAVz4PCu2ELMahsETRshJ8WBZJ0I8mB6LpjUxYdtGDwALZfYO6NOWbvLf1lMbuGBuiPBIVXVI7NN-yT5Qw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/0P08oSk7KAfp3sgqJmiAjdmAUrbTg9FsUlkjAt04xbIVxUf7ynLepPTNCDyS1wSbZIgql3k7g_Adixdu=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/xh-4pEIoXxhU8mA9mLIifuyoQVDCJojBC9-vlXWabqjQ_Z-Dq39NA_w8bC0UiUz_58qRwiYHCS_8sQEl=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/9fmgmhg_vIRoujZARPfuDeoVhQfpkDahJAnJKQFhLr9lzx3Q7uX-h3w3YV1fxpERLQILnsBLlPj4jXCu=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/tP1MO3MBgSoKLW-qH_d6XGjCO5YWtJFzmUuIlxC_EE3ZvUTYNDYQyioIgRsWyDJe03Xbq1JDj5wr7muFXA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/qKoVPTvuVpnZz1vNN6i__nSo-qb8BP0FzlwnidpTbYr_uzpQ3jGZYUT1ve6JTvI8poUrsOkfBeVbU4ULAA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/flh0ornmK0IhUjSPSgIWvPHZj7dhGSr4pVRIHbAhIvN2bQNMqIiOEhdZ_L-1DAE3vz4sX9MPMDtZ9gdk=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/U2iTFYg4SeeJsz1WfGKPhKtJK9v9B0CMMQ2H20FsyBux-nfhhDq1BJi5wQ0nnVUn0u_IKWlqwAcGmfms=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Sv2a_mQmo0CaxNpKa4gw--98Yi0nqL9RNQX60G9qikiIbc4AchePGHSUliKfulzDQSdep1dAKqjD3bqx3A=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/IIhJHbOQWXHzDGouI7piFCkaa9KiI33QNgCnQB29Lux4VP55PJvqRoXe-1VW1Zn6hG0Pdp_tCC2bSbZ2-IM=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/oTlftlOGaJQBLBiqlSeISXbBlkvr1WANgrSi8Dz_pXcTtjC9lHZeZDQVPZPb8xqp-WWFaB27A1fcjS_J=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="17">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/RFVNcWxnE5bJMUl237CTZuhQmmmY_aS4cgXJ-EVDpBd2YI06wySDId59kmLgN2rDEhZulFPm0y9apai0Sg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="18">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/loK-PGXitXYukwZHvJesKc9_W00tnh7cj4m5MdyXPAv3QnUREkGjLQ5Yy5IgxddFdftgaO5Ky46tsdH5wg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="19">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/CsR1s4-zrdhO0FDq5lA1dvZWIp3L7RdRcemS3DfXY-yIMsWckDO422PQavFYle-gE3NwgwV3_uedn6w0lA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="20">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/XHwXNVoZZezmGUiZP3IGyd_jSS-Iln1RTTIYMSvCKWijJXFtQbXCYzhU3Z-gfBaHCZ9mZ3YtQxKAQ0y3ksM=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="21">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/JbvrF-3t-txV_Cw0A6Rkxrg5JXb6_sEDaucyDNQZ61R5ux9Agxx9j0-ys9Eq0BKxYS3pkZJT5eXiWrlk=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="22">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/YIfhEutrL5N_FGTQMujyfaLWo4JTzkDa9ClP2Zb1o2U9giCgWuWFzredv0sRQbSGOB3Vz_88qF-lxM-M=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="23">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/purLvY_sEmr3qTfXNl-C169KpQbI5cLv4zT2Y9kdZW0FKBM7RRTQclPKppnv6RsJsNKIPPfAiczDDfXi=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="24">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/hSHJTc8nnoj4jnkA1G9BT486ozzxSShfp7Xwl0DssIC3ZdgpVXioHQK1agWHp1llu8P5xa1xe-VxmXTZVg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="25">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Fh2fWfPqi5YE8W3r3uVpuzwWqJR8ADV3LiLMX-ygirPUZI3kqqtjUVoXNmSCoY_j0T5v09SmHgm605zXJpM=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="26">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/A5WGDp0XAvTcLDeAAYmopc8GagpbcFtOubSGdjf9M0L1yxHNXBFkpPtbYfgXc7c1VZBCv5frXYsgaYk5VQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="27">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/p5VtFlo3HNmajhmgCtokO6Q5VJu-aV4WrfygoxnXUf6eLU-Mtign0VaVP62_DY4ihIop-0pjm1cuRbNX9w=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="28">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/iomdhc0LZqcdKhtiDsDne7caeQOT5wPtlySMK3j2KAjbOQwfLqio_TyMh0SaPpcezxHUb2rU82feS9SsVQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="29">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/uDoPBJ681h_4JrHLz-Qw5Tj7Q4bUjBzcimvMDux5BRJb6T4buSWfAQMBYg56fnFU6FLgZa03dnSifKMP2H8=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="30">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Pj4xAeCTEqYVJg4LpSHbmc_53Rw2wTjIzcfOx8fdGBCsRlN0NUoLWvs-YgSH2trRyuT9rll9avICLtKl=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="31">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/NDyVHQuqT4NaSqk-9IvFRba7V0adX-tR76YU2QSql9oYv7V9fJXJIM7T4OyCG4e_rQYnPZfZZRxGtmxzeRw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="32">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/o83I66TeANEt63fJ6uN20p6W8368jDm6Nw-rbMxUY1MXsGYE6BDUXU94RUCmmcTGzsPH81o5E8VkoZ-AKQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>15700407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 10:22:04</date>
<ref>TH2-DL-T0010023</ref>
<price>89500</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Townhouse</en>
</type>
<town>Torrevieja</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>Los Balcones</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>1</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
This lovely duplex house with views to the green in Los Balcones (part of southern Torrevieja) is situated in a nice quiet residence. Downstairs the house has a good sized sunny patio with BBQ. Part of the patio could be glazed or built in to enlarge the living space. There is a good sized lounge/dining area which opens to an open plan fully equipped kitchen. Upstairs you find the 2 bedrooms and the family bathroom. The residence is part of a small complex with fantastic facilities to suit all. The large communal pool has an excellent poolside restaurant/bar which caters for all nationalities, tennis courts, petanca courts, small chapel, communal library and beautiful gardens. Within walking distance is a supermarket, bus service into Town, pharmacy, banks, and a number of nice restaurants. Los Balcones is close to sea and beaches,the marina, some golf courses, shopping malls and more.
</en>
<de>
Sehr gepflegte Residenz, ruhig gelegen, perfekt vernetzt per Buslinien mit allen Teilen von Torrevieja (Jachthafen, Zentrum, Shopping, Promenaden, Sandstrände und und und) - hübsches renoviertes Reihenhaus auf 2 Ebenen, spanisches Flair, herrliche Pool- und Restaurantanlage, fussläufig zu allen Versorgungseinrichtungen in Los Balcones - nur ca. 200 m. Natuerlich auch nahe zum Meer und sandigen Badestränden, es wird möbliert verkauft. Anschauen lohnt sich - vereinbaren Sie einen Termin mit den Team von maxgoldhouse.
</de>
<fr>
Cette belle maison mitoyenne avec vue sur le vert à Los Balcones (partie du sud de Torrevieja) se trouve dans une belle résidence calme. La maison dispose d'un grand patio ensoleillé avec barbecue. Une partie du patio offre un espace pour une extension pour augmenter l'espace de vie si désiré. Le salon / salle à manger spacieux dispose d'une cuisine ouverte et est entièrement équipée. A l'étage, vous trouverez les 2 chambres et la salle de bains. La propriété fait partie d'un petit complexe avec des commodités fantastiques. À la grande piscine commune, vous trouverez un excellent restaurant / bar avec un menu varié! De plus, le complexe comprend des courts de tennis, des courts de pétanque, une petite chapelle, une bibliothèque partagée et de beaux jardins. À distance de marche, il y a un supermarché, un arrêt de bus pour la ville, une pharmacie, des banques et des restaurants agréables. Los Balcones est proche de la mer et des plages, de la marina, des terrains de golf, des centres commerciaux et bien plus encore!
</fr>
<nl>
Deze mooie rijwoning met uitzicht op het groen in Los Balcones (onderdeel van zuidelijk Torrevieja) ligt in een mooie, rustige residentie. Het huis heeft een grote, zonnige patio met barbecue. Een deel van de patio biedt, indien gewenst, ruimte voor een aanbouw om de woonruimte te vergroten. De ruime woon- / eetkamer heeft een open, compleet uitgeruste keuken. Op de bovenverdieping vindt u de 2 slaapkamers en de badkamer. De woning is onderdeel van een klein complex met fantastische faciliteiten. Aan het grote, gemeenschappelijke zwembad vindt u een uitstekend restaurant/bar met een uitgebreide menukaart! Daarnaast beschikt het complex over tennisbanen, petanqueveldjes, een kleine kapel, gemeenschappelijke bibliotheek en mooie tuinen. Op loopafstand is een supermarkt, bushalte naar de stad, een apotheek, banken en een aantal leuke restaurants. Los Balcones ligt dichtbij zee en stranden, de jachthaven, golfbanen, winkelcentra en nog veel meer!
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/yr9mB_4ly_sYfmJNqB2U9NCP2YrtMcdg-ihcZcF6vzcBw-dMEotObTlH6Ui9o_Ucq_kKXqZSFLZJw_TKCg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/hDhjv68qh1pdqsXFD1VRl4KOsXlJyoJSKX431exd7IsSScHwydOGMFKQ1x_iX3gATK00A82HfMearXUpz0c=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/yCVa7IaI-8ps_fC0wjtJvy37KYExe4Y_PWlXR8enZUxPwQvDG5v2acnyB97DojKX4gx7XQ0n8TbgjOxC1w=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/crrAgc_uAM1kdg5RcC_X7bpYWdpBdC1A6BvHOsld7j06x5HzK2_JEGKuAkvvH0O5WYqLtmacV6rvte_Dr5U=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/4dXn1OU0ie8dPyigXKme8vyJjOKyeFh5En8G2l1ZKxVXNENena2Idn__aORFVH0qmwMohKGAaCTWvRvkig=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/3cGOwhGKUSY6_T3dHosGRC6u8_PkDbb5TEC86erxvtJ7c6ovjXlp6BbuzCCOWjVoDc4K_TPmOsei2qUJfoY=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/J_JLd_U--1aioA_Oyy0RPDbTRK1hYysCRe7sVJtOuKbMeRa4IgDEUkQ3bpK7bmwNqTPRlP1TJfU9MDXv=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1RtgMLQiiGDw2RP2ZXMQcQHXsflrcBli3vUw8LbCNyVQK8P8y6CZ1fp6kCyW6R-bi2COGjPZt300i5_8=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/QnWbksTR2C4bpKtpW6Oukc3-Qrurcf4ZPDqXPE7OX4tCVaILYRtU5fewHyusqK0HgWgNXngehHEDBs_Rhw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/IMaGycQHvBu0-7EWstn3bIGBnBpiHe0HNW5m5d6lMJzjrr_jknc55xy2-IVnfHpjrIXOgoErQfXY7CYQiw0=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/cQlQz9QWdwd3s7fdevgLhMsNKS_v620_ErSJGoLIUsL6nW7WCIOfujvzfkfI6r73UIBIFRhQWv1gb0OEpg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/RaB51fWTUsD3I8lD5cjT8LllKp3S4zgcOut11OoOHNaBi30wBYidrkTUWPPO7vXh1SiMtagyLOjnuoGTVnw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/et94ZEINlNAkI_0YtFdcsq6iPjJdhoiQFTStBw9a9fPSgfsWIA7NDoQ9GzdEAfRSUDYAaqBj3WOhUYnUGg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/uUa2UaI1NlN-L6YeCaVD7a6y21jGUpLOHiQaptiqPJUG-5n3mNbodA8jEW2wq-EYTBu3f13f0Moxbv3guQA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/cEH3dM_gcIYSu0Hwdqvgw3M8iIwUfzFDB4uMyJ9CxfVsFT2ZWxLhroXT8ZJC0OQ4VF3L1vxwb-TyNf4w=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dWM6BgoI0zz7yqa_sykpYkR2vMMfUA-3srfEfU7cRzkWnEpOLal86pFeiPR5Dd9CCHic6KTPi2RfOGgX=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="17">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/DZ3yTQpiReAr5n7sMedsT05d03mkwxjn658e1FaWfc386Pzjf6y65fUjsL_LEF4pSjBGPOv0UToyFOjd=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="18">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/R23Kv2rNOuTvvc-XO5ygfAfdfFES3-XqZFdnTJLJl3jsnE0gH2Kl9kQD6oBUjDFtnQatMEM-rcy7uizsslI=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>16170407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 14:35:13</date>
<ref>AP2-DL-C00220</ref>
<price>89900</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Apartment</en>
</type>
<town>Orihuela Costa</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>Cabo Roig</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>1</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
Modern 2nd Floor seaview apartment in Lomas de Cabo Roig - beach, sea, water sports, golf, etc. - this property in the Cabo Roig / Orihuela Costa area offers pure Spanish lifestyle living. Four golf courses are just minutes away and also the picturesque marina and lovely cafes and restaurants - and not to forget the daily shopping! This property is located just a short walk from local bars, shops, restaurant, supermarkets and the local bus stop. The golden sandy beaches of Campoamor and Cabo Roig are also closeby. This is a perfect investment in a well kept residential area. Another maxgoldhouse offer. Come and see.
</en>
<de>
Sehr schön gelegenes OG Apartment in Lomas de Cabo Roig nahe zu Villamartin. Gepflegte Residenz, grosse Poolanlage. Kurzer Wege zu allen Versorgungseinrichtungen - die perfekte Lage. Gut eingerichtet, herrlicher Gemeinschaftspool, wird möbliert verkauft - eine gepflegte Immobilie in einer bequemen Lage - Cabo Roig /Villamartin bietet alles was man so braucht - grosse Einkaufzentren, viele Restaurants, das gesamte Jahr hindurch aktiv und offen - und ist nahe zum Meer mit feinen Sandstränden, Wassersporteinrichtungen, Jachthafen - und vieles mehr.
</de>
<fr>
Appartement moderne avec vue sur la mer au 2ème étage à Lomas de Cabo Roig, près de la plage, de la mer, des sports nautiques, etc. Cette propriété à Cabo Roig / Orihuela Costa vous offre un style de vie purement espagnol. À quelques minutes de quatre terrains de golf, la marina pittoresque, de beaux cafés, restaurants, l'arrêt de bus local - sans parler des magasins pour vos courses quotidiennes! Les plages de sable doré de Campoamor et Cabo Roig sont également à proximité. C'est l'investissement parfait dans une résidence bien entretenue. Offert par Maxgoldhouse, venez jeter un coup d'œil!
</fr>
<nl>
Modern appartement met zeezicht op de 2e verdieping in Lomas de Cabo Roig, vlak bij strand, zee, watersporten, enz. Deze eigendom in Cabo Roig / Orihuela Costa biedt u een pure Spaanse levensstijl. Op slechts enkele minuten afstand van vier golfbanen, de pittoreske jachthaven, leuke cafés, restaurants, de lokale bushalte - en niet te vergeten winkels voor uw dagelijkse boodschappen! De gouden zandstranden van Campoamor en Cabo Roig zijn ook vlakbij. Dit is de perfecte investering in een goed onderhouden residentie. Aangeboden door Maxgoldhouse, kom snel kijken!
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/SixSLSxeLKEXZ1-RU2kdEh5P7xFpirQ0IXkwVXmuUJPQnSJppfuHUckEkcAl5m5W_NJTMb53wEoGCdA2Ag=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/T7joo9ncvjE5zQjAl9fqS-tlcgb3A9QjWCNoHPO0fAJCTMRbZc5mnBha6A-jQ4DRVU7NdV9mBg6YOf9O=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/qcpNWjvGVlCF1TAHiWDoxhPRp_-grTLTwONmbR6h5mgcfMr1wFCb4tBHZDL9nsSM6qv4E5jDqhVyNjHx=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Pqa8Bm6URSKSGSX4WZdFYiF3pROooOdjI8HA1bkUvqgEkeBaBX8LlQF1oajqVILmB7XKv8qWJhMYJVcz=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/9ZpNFEfwK89y04i-FpIjB8dt140UMwldpKIo0E2WUiT4oIxNq6GVjUNgKHll3A2DLx0QmFhB7XTX6yod4VU=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/zw618EMAjGo_2dyaY1Io68I7UTWi-ihPb2GCJ2RfXwjtGID0JBCceC3HG63EHqN5-LKvsW1e_DuuIAkg1Q=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/WKqztgg7V8-HP0tURARK3xCY9FtSBYjPKtztN-kG09JiU8zv8retceDyKpggfXA9cy28m44UoOJ1FDR7jY8=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/FjVj_Zi5cQwrEOuHUVcI3F5oHEzmCXgII6Xui-S3beY8ALSy6ogCaNl17rnWqq0Mzo7Jql2W7GwtrVRG3w=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/CTcU7xZZg7sl5dn2tLtIjI2WoQeQvfNN5zlBiCUlnA33J5Jxv0mwInKsxvqAo1jIQ3kxVhCTc22uESLDquQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/AFGICR4FiNAwduN8v3QC101f48XJ3OjoaiBIrJyKSAveAwXPHcuAtgu9-_g4IFt4h-0krhKhC7LtfYZhiQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/PI6J1YnEb3MYJBkn2yevvQ3JmoHsD2Ivad0U6w1vioMRa6_qXdKko0I82bNGsSH9j_4etbaxjACSRtnQ6w=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/QeVM1M9vCZr6qFfy015JdcsHEqChVj_tZneCyS5QiU0YrmTGF7_dsOjkaxFZK9yZiNb1glMOV_y3KBPH=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/zZAOdAzB9VVn8IjYP_lbDHu4mhu5OzIkcVQ4WX1gSq-a8LUovh1kxpzgjmdgKc3YF7VJGdk91SLYoFzmkw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/XCTzbSZshMjyMLz-z2GeDG0D1rkVy-TkiF8T3xj7VxWtlxULHwnsU2S0pXtdzLB7zzhPOUvyCCA5OZlD6g=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/w5528aCw_urfntRRmbtifBGvl1LW4EMnAuM34qRqhhoXU7HfX73cEgSipqkMQye6hk8LU6a3VOwX-TqX=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/_WG-a-mAcf5wsDz1Cw2yDP6iV86_giFh8IBlAK0EEDRLcoOV4S7cu_5ycrD-uGEJS3Ms4EUoHq-7hTpAng=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="17">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ngEuxhEKid0hNre_C6XdyX2DwpxHBlXn7hCIJ5IChyd_Od9Q0YPa0YCt9LtUdcz7rFyPgCmn8GlA1nZO=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="18">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/UYawxXxJilIXsxupPzCgRIh6axqsV-dfPGUNWFJHmuNTLEQxdXkjQZXJtd9SSstT2fxYwDpLfDAFGGj8Gg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="19">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/uEiwYQTb3Mj5Dc3ca_onbmBzh4zqpqHV2KqtiSCEKFSF8Rgq7B1j9k__m2OCNS0VH4M9rL-bMhYyXSeoDg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="20">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/BklH8-qqzRsX7i31qIlzf9ZSzCpUiY7C1XzOiwBFiEo9WCc-K-U9EpBGJ4sy5-cj_zEBjIhiMiHqpcMF=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="21">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ag__WB6BHYlLqsMhfGMFrrrpAmQZLb3wCmuV1kMBpDOB64jwHtUrlOaOe90H9Q8bHqQ2AZxV3pwVCSqlbF0=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="22">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/7R_0joRYGkwCkX858iaxVt0u3D55rQLqBvD5EG7Tb4dmpO0WfrwjkVYulk5ahIWcYZigrlNvXfbONj7cfA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="23">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/JhmeKGfo8SJi1fHnzb1p6CqFbnxnlJOIdSmmj3rRJo_qe1Q8Ewpsk9LAVKhC1_QF9pW-eU998hgFKZ3pB9Y=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>17820407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 07:41:20</date>
<ref>AP2-DL-PPMI253</ref>
<price>89999</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Apartment</en>
</type>
<town>Orihuela Costa</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>Punta Prima</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>1</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
This well presented, south facing, top floor apartment in Punta Prima is a must see! With 2 bedrooms, one large bathroom and a seperate kitchen, this cosy apartment is an holiday home. Not only is there a communal pool and terrace, there is also a large solarium which has sea views so you can enjoy all day sunshine whilst enjoying the view! Next to the ever popular Torrevieja offering a lot of restaurants, lovely beach, wonderful national parks, salt lakes and natural forest zones there is plenty to see and visit! Contact Maxgoldhouse for a viewing today!!
</en>
<de>
Diese gepflegte, nach Süden ausgerichtete Dachgeschosswohnung in Punta Prima ist ein Muss! Das gemütliche Apartment ist eingerichtet mit 2 Schlafzimmern, einem großen Badezimmer und einer separaten Küche. Es gibt nicht nur einen Gemeinschaftspool und eine Terrasse, sondern auch eine große Sonnenterrasse mit Meerblick, so dass Sie den ganzen Tag Sonnenschein genießen können! Neben dem allseits beliebten Torrevieja mit vielen Restaurants, schönen Stränden, wunderschönen Nationalparks, Salzseen und natürlichen Waldgebieten gibt es viel zu sehen und zu besuchen ! Kontaktieren Sie Maxgoldhouse für eine Besichtigung - am besten noch heute!
</de>
<fr>
Cet appartement bien exposé et plein sud au dernier étage de Punta Prima est un must see! Avec 2 chambres, une grande salle de bains et une cuisine séparée, cet appartement confortable est une vraie maison de vacances. Non seulement il y a une piscine commune et une terrasse, mais il y a aussi un grand solarium avec vue sur la mer, de sorte que vous pouvez profiter du soleil toute la journée tout en profitant de la vue! Outre le très populaire Torrevieja avec ses nombreux restaurants, sa magnifique plage, ses magnifiques parcs nationaux, ses lacs salés et ses forêts naturelles, il y a beaucoup à voir et à visiter! Contactez Maxgoldhouse aujourd'hui pour une visite!
</fr>
<nl>
Dit goed gepresenteerde, op het zuiden gelegen appartement op de bovenste verdieping in Punta Prima is een must see! Met 2 slaapkamers, een grote badkamer en een aparte keuken, is dit gezellige appartement een echt vakantiehuis. Niet alleen is er een gemeenschappelijk zwembad en een terras, er is ook een groot solarium met uitzicht op zee, zodat u de hele dag kunt genieten van de zon terwijl u geniet van het uitzicht! Buiten het altijd populaire Torrevieja met veel restaurants, prachtig strand, prachtige nationale parken, zoutmeren en natuurlijke bosgebieden is er verder nog genoeg te zien en te bezoeken! Neem vandaag nog contact op met Maxgoldhouse voor een bezichtiging !!
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/5hUDyY0H_yET_n6WIX77c0fyS8i8Ecqc795uPUJ40OiCOkrM8jGWjNzDUKLetNxCbW2776erb8MnkfpBjxQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/9QaL1eruFQgsxpXiAxcN7NMuRZ3IK4T6YRyHKaWlJ2kDBd4pv5avItR-O_og26Yup8sGe5l4vzRld3tj=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/FsH75TM8gqRpVZfsBc8EmMvMF4Y1nPRrQj4NZra-TSnY3UM5jrXoDOR8MDzz22VP6phmADIJiX0CBH8GMQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-hwENw6i0Ytnra6C24bNe05pra8JXllw3p_aHKMMZufaZpLOLh2GWEn8R2GST_yMhW5ab6P_xLs-AUNSOw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/JeSjpC7Zt3QznuApIRxjYmr6xavrZwS7u0BDEoL9mLbyTHnlnwbgmFvJiifOVHTtG4nMWhkPvAEOI76pmjo=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/FGW16qHlTf7qmiRiHA2UrucGrM3m1DaKjCxdfikt2pK579hoZXdNFzGE1zjBNaCOdx51dY8V3_1weJSk=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/7xz3K25uxUsOg0G76Tpc3tjqEfyb5WQL3OCfQBFEl1iQvfKksJT6c5P5bH4uW3999CpTJeznc2DH5VUqFQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/6Tp1M0M4hLh1cvNaEbrzrR2hXEPZz1ddVwgKfUVazPkflbmtsgZjO-e_SFHdZkDXzxIeKAKkpnIX4mMq=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/4jgpybr5Xzy6BDHdf0pI5RB714Uy7Bbpgh76vNOiKNgXz_EimS4pB4djh1vbqDsFt6PfhjVU6G7n81ZN=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dGCjN01kmuv7i3425xSPz-9AmEc7gscWecFNpKLUjSHvQEzz4OpZ-1zX4-3AErYu6DQX-92BKFCwg87IMg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/I-_3A4wXvg0YzkxdhKn0LvktivWu0xxKff4SYWBr4Vdk_X1q7W-cO8yAy7B3vhaQ88ug2PeRmtvs8dshGw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1m1dIWMlKQDCKxedngBvgSWjqhvplhYX2sg2gOvn6gNSR13Mc_2SGPuyWNHWyYQJbJR3M02aXEuKu_3h9Q=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/d_jpzDDPX0XDLjvdgpb_RnK7KLniMC1xkro55Bt8CRc3E6KX5zXG3ip5zYmcPWVPgLiR2lMzvQdVNGm0=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Xz5gVpCtbDLado5jrxZ07cJGqFOigv_8smLOf31ZC6oocmbEaSVyQLXZ2kv__0k9-CZv_Fuof5jQO9TUTg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/zx0rhdC2fGtQbMb0fOmbbzPhrew_LwXQOAUiWsKlbrXkDKvrWVzrL6vIHwwXw06DL-F1kvykbFwzEbPg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/L-Z6CEH3Vncn4iw4FRCK5extPgNB8r826xu1Ubu3HcLwmRxvFdeeQK2KWo6twQlzNuralyWM0jeSWypteeI=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="17">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/tRCby7T-XeKDfLCtEWycMMetqTlsmAF-NEw0DlTex1_z7-rIC2GL0araFdHpF1vNFCh7ppF8vaEFf70hclM=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="18">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/V33oJUEvxpUWIDM2ci5-rdTjoBMFi_CMADt0wnA5yLOCPcbsV--WTFPHx5RAOimS2CLs3fqyFd8zimlJeQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="19">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/LMfCD4mWxuSN1VFp-xhoIg9SxUZkfSDf0X9Yaeik4V1VnksRW9ZdTQSRbRVlLkDrIZQvBvLuXK3tkNDpdg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="20">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/9a9M0E5sLK-n1Bw6KHvlPyHtzFju3jbDzMiHBF9Da3xlVWBLBPrTeU6tGUpQaKDq5jli1XPrz5ff50_rDw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="21">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/QThpm0wLjpiI1zM4YS_nretPz17z7BeyaphweCiuUzNwOm3FGF1h3EV1zCCeR2p3ogtu0745swETsCzsYlU=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="22">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/F7GqTG6VNVgB5bkKC9PZYiOBTivALIUHqF31TPLf0f35hhrwmytQEl_h-HU9wH9nMAmoykezOKa0l5bwLQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="23">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/0GBVWKbRvUhy0PkdHMZD37jVd3OBFrslIy0soEiJADIqCxxHZSwMTErQFoIK3GTZGk44P-blzOFuW_vLPA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="24">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/DtVM0KJ-djEgdudjg69IKosOV11EDIzggixo4kTMjCWensHeC10xV6eEN59ATibyASl7Vl7q1IFBGyQB300=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="25">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/31dZlDi8RZ3wj7ccj4eavyTFkd05qeJh3TtatyF-puGJyMsHQbXeKISHSB0k5lgLEjbAMOo4IlRBQFIb3A=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>16460407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 10:44:28</date>
<ref>TH2-DL-PF001278</ref>
<price>114900</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Townhouse</en>
</type>
<town>Orihuela Costa</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>Playa Flamenca</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>2</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
Dreamy townhouse in Playa Flamenca with views over the lovely communal pool and green area. This home offers 2 bedrooms, 1 bathroom, guest toilet and 30m2 patio/BBQ area. Inside you find the inviting living room with open stairway and separate fully fitted kitchen. To be sold fully furnished. Enjoy a nice, cosy family BBQ on the patio or hop into the pool that is just outside your door! Located very close to the La Florida shopping centre. Playa Flamenca offers everything you want including nice bars and restaurants, the Saturday market, the famous LA ZENIA BOULEVARD shopping mall, sea and beaches and all kinds of water sports. The development is close to several golf courses. Come and see!
</en>
<de>
Traumhaus in Playa Flamenca mit Blick auf den schönen Gemeinschaftspool und die grüne Umgebung. Dieses Reihenhaus verfügt über 2 Schlafzimmer, 1 Badezimmer, Gäste-WC und 30m2 Terrasse / Grillplatz. Im Inneren finden Sie das einladende Wohnzimmer mit offener Treppe und eine separate, voll ausgestattete Küche. Wird komplett möbliert verkauft. Genießen Sie einen lustigen, gemütlichen Familiengrill auf der Terrasse oder springen Sie direkt vor der Tür ins Schwimmbecken! Das Haus liegt sehr nahe am Einkaufszentrum von La Florida. Playa Flamenca bietet Ihnen alles, was Sie wollen, einschließlich großer Bars und Restaurants, dem Samstagsmarkt, dem berühmten Einkaufszentrum LA ZENIA BOULEVARD, Meer und Strand, allen Arten von Wassersportarten und verschiedenen Golfplätzen. Komm und sieh selbst!
</de>
<fr>
Maison de rêve à Playa Flamenca donnant sur la belle piscine communale et les environs verdoyants. Cette maison mitoyenne offre 2 chambres, 1 salle de bain, toilettes invités et 30m2 patio / barbecue. A l'intérieur, vous trouverez le salon accueillant avec escalier ouvert et une cuisine séparée entièrement équipée. Sera vendu entièrement meublé. Profitez d'un barbecue familial amusant sur la terrasse ou sautez dans la piscine juste devant la porte! La maison est très proche du centre commercial de La Florida. Playa Flamenca vous offre tout ce que vous voulez, y compris de grands bars et restaurants, le marché du samedi, le célèbre centre commercial LA ZENIA BOULEVARD, la mer et la plage, toutes sortes de sports nautiques et divers terrains de golf. Venez voir par vous-même!
</fr>
<nl>
Droomhuis in Playa Flamenca met uitzicht op het mooie gemeenschappelijke zwembad en de groene omgeving. Deze rijwoning biedt 2 slaapkamers, 1 badkamer, gastentoilet en 30m2 patio / BBQ- ruimte. Binnen vindt u de uitnodigende woonkamer met open trap en een aparte, volledig ingerichte keuken. Wordt volledig gemeubileerd verkocht. Geniet van een leuke, gezellige familie-BBQ op het terras of spring in het zwembad dat net voor de deur ligt! De woning ligt zeer dichtbij het winkelcentrum van La Florida. Playa Flamenca biedt u alles wat je wilt, inclusief leuke bars en restaurants, de zaterdagmarkt, het beroemde winkelcentrum LA ZENIA BOULEVARD, zee en strand, allerlei watersporten en verschillende golfbanen. Kom zelf kijken!
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/eqQrJwvLm8aL1C3AIs51V4EJR-Xdi3ArEDS8R5IxzSv27JXh1lB2FxgOiWFDQviAjttoZkY0uhYKKxXS=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/fu8FYvOsIj3lk-J7fBuwOsKOGV8TRjG-qVN6EjQHSwLnGkP2f-TVePSwo81ASpQhgiE-fKiKyhqKOb1j=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/n4Sy2iyZBWIijq_BUgaTsCRFE4N7it5nQlLmPGsaksU1hliFXCkZTPGQJts3ttNV5JCuK9UgIc5PITKY=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ec-kjJrW7H5qrVhxRXl0gPjj_1g6b84F_X0d-xbqxjkfxnxSn97Q8fubVBIwe9cgV3G3zToFRN4a0l0oiQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/tMCdgYCqCXuyp060y5PPC9n26ZIbobX0qAssQfrWqgolix3gdEOBFDgQCiAwKAyj-ojFNOqKzO2NCAqR=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1OgR4aH-kQI2YQMB7tCK1jbfgdQOvxQx-FgbKfdODbgw0cZvLdmjwYTwWCJ6xjctEguGvizUN49_l4VzmQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/u56P-4iNvqqSAo_eppC6YOd-uofR1nLlu0Y3533xOnEAYQbFPiGbKsiyJHrMgIuzKWBuTPKKMXUtS-KH1FQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Fov6JGTO9d7efkuayzJPSB2_5nFBqrtFavkQQdGe2pQZQK8L7GIONc1bo5Ci0fWQjuNuPvDPnXo6FZxHGQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/UBTK54Ei-d9yG-_mEj6yt93q8gpQj7AwixBWqGmB4KI5v4kd4BKqUek8t7CkMWydWdzxFU9f1zbzGYZM=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1pWX4BcYm05mAByD5q8wal3jw73vIjvG6I1rrZ3wmvpShX0Du2KVmiTD_adSruWG3G5SlwTTVh85aTiMCg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/_jeYicmLgcDKcPlLpLDDkMt2lYbHEBrD2wDL-nnpFSTwvYUp2PMfmvVJzPXLgYMFkilYZwG_Ms_3u2qBbg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/zqbu0Hk7WXNh-RbUu_tjjWtzaqeQK5OWAUyorDbXxD7a_8vw5B10nLo8LYfoI7ca5rxlW2Pk9V7miwfiAA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/CRvwPDf-Y0WuZAhdYDRm0zELduRZk5hubMMYZv8Wlx6G--5xxCS1WOsp8XjmUdyLUCmsqruqK-NRmJeR=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/YmkRC-ctfHAdYw4Ct6K4yw8oG5g2QqkEs9QehGoMlANwusLTU4dAhstCw54p9XqPdNfE8iqWki8u-ml05Q=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/D7LV2BqkrFTb_Fd02Irl13p9O_2JNNJLtntjgWDgstuARZIuPubGsZp6vZygTaYOObDUgMCFweOOR7MdKA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/E1LM0Tmr2Os6g9SKm-LtI072wXiybuBDNe36DVWIGVRC2EekULCfFXNwxTm6Sa1sNXTnXpaCPzpjme9lvQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="17">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/QPvYQlSj-_Nv65cicfSkQjXkkLRJCmptp3QlLXcOJWwceXFwEIv2-3NEwftRuhH0Fwa373uHu3T-8_I_=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="18">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2-mqBC-ApRbO-fnDKahgV6H8a6dPphYgc2u13uAXgWxrkUh11KbzlQF6aLnU5PyHd5ElJfHhB_LjsUbbsw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>16710407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 12:00:50</date>
<ref>AP2-DL-CMI231</ref>
<price>115000</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Apartment</en>
</type>
<town>Orihuela Costa</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>Campoamor</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>1</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
This spacious pool view apartment in the sought after Campoamor offers that purely Spanish way of living. The golden sandy beaches of Campoamor and Cabo Roig, the picturesque marina, lovely cafes and restaurants and five international golf courses are only a few minutes away. This property is located just a short walk from all needed amenities: supermarkets, local bars, shops and the local bus stop. This is a perfect investment in a well kept residential area. Another Maxgoldhouse offer. Come and see.
</en>
<de>
Diese geräumige Wohnung mit Blick auf den Pool im beliebten Campoamor bietet Ihnen die pure spanische Lebensart. Die goldenen Sandstrände von Campoamor und Cabo Roig, der malerische Yachthafen, nette Cafés, Restaurants und fünf internationale Golfplätze sind nur wenige Minuten entfernt. Diese Eigenschaft ist nur einen kurzen Spaziergang von allen notwendigen Annehmlichkeiten: Supermärkte, Bars, Geschäfte und die Bushaltestelle. Dies ist eine perfekte Investition in einer gepflegten Wohngegend. Ein weiteres Angebot von Maxgoldhouse, komm und schau dich kurz um!
</de>
<fr>
Cet appartement spacieux donnant sur la piscine dans le populaire Campoamor vous offre ce pur style de vie espagnol. Les plages de sable doré de Campoamor et de Cabo Roig, le port de plaisance pittoresque, les beaux cafés, les restaurants et les cinq parcours de golf internationaux sont à quelques minutes. Cette propriété est juste une courte promenade de toutes les commodités nécessaires: les supermarchés, les bars locaux, les magasins et l'arrêt de bus local. C'est un investissement parfait dans un quartier résidentiel bien entretenu. Une autre offre de Maxgoldhouse, venez jeter un coup d'œil!
</fr>
<nl>
Dit ruime appartement met uitzicht op het zwembad in het populaire Campoamor biedt u die puur Spaanse manier van leven. De gouden zandstranden van Campoamor en Cabo Roig, de pittoreske jachthaven, leuke cafés, restaurants en vijf internationale golfbanen liggen op slechts een paar minuten afstand. Deze woning ligt op slechts een korte wandeling van alle benodigde voorzieningen: supermarkten, lokale bars, winkels en de lokale bushalte. Dit is een perfecte investering in een goed onderhouden woonwijk. Weer een aanbieding van Maxgoldhouse, kom snel kijken!
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/rPi6FpzEF7jeHNfU_-d6uNZsL3U1SbYmczEZFucVPfZ1Riysv5JT518arzQmn-NPV77uzk0VMaX2_ULy=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/0y1wmg5LXtz1ombnMZjViirtHUeZmFnz6VZ7UiaU_0P6i83Yo2_qLVKZKSl5n1TSHm21KC2XcwZwkkGhbA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/AAatOaMUoNhoM6lczpBV0zAucHF_a2CdMyAcPPzLLgpgsbKDkakucYnuBJIpCwKS7sPtun0DNhd5oJD-UQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/hI3MQuhng0fGczNs4_Q-dDYsdDw-aR2CUHM4e4OEJ8PFjdNr_YSM_t3elScpQ-o7uVkRjmc-_YFnxv1X=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/9Ko_a_3VFpnat_xw4WG5l55LN2iD4qT2ucS27ZOC4Us2hWnv64xuxwMQRhc0BytHWTmdunT591gH47mnJw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/E9iEbAeONg4-R7f8zyuAHDw1Bj6DAOzewrXHB9RMDLTxUWH7_cbAkflA2qJFaAwwPSdDQu99b8d2J-5irrM=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/7_uDpqRuTm_hWe_6PBAU9bjhwVhTwZRNtbj93Q0-jp-p-c4kcIJ2NzjqXz0TqIiI9bfeVWcVWr6ABUpi=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/KGzA8SfHtzXO88Vw7yvtnOgYswQt0_E3syxiBMjj9Ldb4F46rNClMtwyopBSNIQtr9bpl83uCiYG5S4bzw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/yyb1RwrtsZ4INApGRAkriLp-O0OYwQ71YwZAtAF_JfCdICCl2qGigJP6IxLY8didL0R_pLGhJyq9k1FB0LE=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/83BmkqEhUEzeuWdhk9QdKvtq-76pPWpeGKPw33YOTC30MRvqRIWXfks4vvS5beUJZkGTRpLmchrbtosW=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/a_kreSZd_rOKXtjxzE6quxjmJPxNvzNMz--o7Tgl78mmcz6G_BMBz4rRhLE-52Ai84m2iCTMBKqG8mG0AA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/w-PcOGjSuBMDueHoFpuaySzXiS3E1uz-13cWSZG1dWcUxYnboAk57E4Zp6-py8GQngn2VpbFVIwr1VCL3xg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/xiTdOZFTBAOrHvydzXVbmCE_--Rj8gMqcYT6wfXqzAH0gcVGhj-ySdYORh0YpFDqkZrPdKXGi_Lk4bEd=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/cCXVZXR3ocoyWmjyLFT7mC5VS6GJfWQ2pUx3d3qNGN6gABVtAt-l9BNwvlXQvm7DNIOAvrZLgYWhMI3s=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/p3aNHSd8_AMv5P8S14DWXSRcrKH37TghYNd0PNk05gYEbgYcbLND3VDEQlGsCXaCax1p5GqDH3JBIMnBFg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/3gTKMwhhRim3uLDXRJiWkCsavuEPauZ2in3tqkt1h6Yg-UlGar2UsERWvTQTpWld4lEe67IVYhk1Fo95gWo=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="17">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2fWVk8SgQljtcnr8sBIUrARnySxRCWk6B0yNy1O8eFAbsTlsq2K2-bCkp9fsLBeIj0wEV7ViWTi_cHJX=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="18">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/vXJyswPzDC4wFTi5EM2p-t9kRxw9BcRBKP9QPJP8Q10jyDtdIIUhjTcHLyZxCrXBQ9uau-fF0rsgwnxQOg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="19">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/m4rdJn-5Y5MaHjW1Oqbdm_QkUHFxCiJlxU5IsCzbgIY0m69IpfGhu-fuJBgelA3LWj6Ud0cAvKGXyvrSaA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="20">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/UhwW35XJpf8cXX6l-NRuY9S9zot_5tnuIYfRL7tU7dKrnOc6LD-tvIUEGS6VCoYCxlA0SpBVE16X1DV3sA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="21">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/08ia9Dr9cES5obwBb21l6mbIBiN3PLhU4AKzexswijHZCRxu1L5K3xR7RvRqi1bhtutl3WRuq28OhmziE3g=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="22">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/304M-ppTxHBh-cp8ZMGu6PhXF-FjzTWswcOz8Bx-rVrjp6UdBMiIkz2ePzljnXScVlI1KXkcf20MDsGWLWY=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="23">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/VWYdUC6VIUMpmRYz5aK9z7cpJkRCMM9jfa7iDC4ClrR1HPKZx5cdjeu1Ex-Z3HvY9QHY1MZAFb6qhi24LQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="24">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Pb8nAynezPxb6_zSpgKzd1izRvKcni7JlKgsgXH7o-ypYhAGqGR2stJDAPgovv-QLEI3k0MAGZZmZkYlLDk=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="25">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Tb_njTXVeKoR2DsaF-3vgUTNKxKmtJyjgAkSvJ4d_y7bP1oC2RyPa6nwn5FBj6DAOT2bMuwlzJ3dCr6dRQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>16680407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 16:02:13</date>
<ref>AP2-DL-PP00229</ref>
<price>120000</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Apartment</en>
</type>
<town>Orihuela Costa</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>Punta Prima</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>1</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
This sea front apartment only a few steps from the Rocio del Mar beach and the famous Nautilus restaurant is a must see! Because of the terrace on 2 sides of the apartment, you do not have only fantastic sea views, but also an amazing view over the green areas. Could not be better!! The apartments has 2 bedrooms, 1 bathroom, and is sold fully equipped and furnished. It has airconditioning, a community pool and a garage included in the price. Make your appointment with MAXGOLDHOUSE now
</en>
<de>
Dieses Strandapartment befindet sich nur einen Steinwurf vom Strand von Rocio del Mar entfernt und das berühmte Restaurant Nautilus ist ein Muss! Diese Wohnung hat einen Balkon auf zwei Seiten, so dass Sie nicht nur einen fantastischen Meerblick, sondern auch einen tollen Blick auf das Grün haben. Es kann nicht besser sein !! Die Wohnung verfügt über 2 Schlafzimmer, 1 Badezimmer und wird komplett ausgestattet und möbliert verkauft. Darüber hinaus gibt es eine Klimaanlage, einen Gemeinschaftspool und eine Garage, die im Preis inbegriffen ist. Vereinbaren Sie jetzt einen Termin bei MAXGOLDHOUSE.
</de>
<fr>
Cet appartement de plage juste à deux pas de la plage de Rocio del Mar et du célèbre restaurant Nautilus est un ‘MUST SEE’! Cet appartement dispose d'un balcon sur deux côtés, de sorte que vous avez non seulement une vue fantastique sur la mer, mais aussi une belle vue sur le vert. Ça ne peut pas être mieux !! L'appartement dispose de 2 chambres, 1 salle de bain et est vendu entièrement équipé et meublé. En outre, il y a la climatisation, une piscine commune et un garage qui est inclus dans le prix. Prenez rendez-vous chez MAXGOLDHOUSE maintenant.
</fr>
<nl>
Dit strandappartement op slechts een steenworp afstand van het strand Rocio del Mar en het beroemde restaurant Nautilus, is een ‘MUST SEE’! Dit appartement heeft aan twee zijden een balkon, hierdoor heeft u niet alleen een fantastisch uitzicht op zee, maar ook een geweldig uitzicht op het groen. Het kan niet beter!! Het appartement heeft 2 slaapkamers, 1 badkamer en wordt volledig uitgerust en gemeubileerd verkocht. Verder is er airconditioning, een gemeenschappelijk zwembad en een garage die bij de prijs inbegrepen is. Maak nu een afspraak bij MAXGOLDHOUSE.
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/HqKPkdZpyE9tX9mJlfWnRyV6XqBR3wYnbqjfMHEwP1vO15sg_ADiViUv6Cz5HHCXSCABc6D-yqVBZqerOSM=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/sfEDUfZFL9T72lB99qjY3jw5x9Bk3JnxLDjwD5J73l6AKmoAXPaCnE5h-PYkjRC5RQkMX_5qvtnUd3MJ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/WRcQZBMQnCIyAMExklH48S2kc-NSR0v-iO9Y9fitBlUxFJpUYdZ6MT_QxiwaFVHAgFv3nX4y8FHgMDdBlXE=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/7Kx9wMsdsO6k3CuTPs_XumaJDGY0ep7aKsZ7NhavBT1CUSTCWNduiMYg1apHaTkETw7vUOYmQ9mAdvek=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ijNG_jB06L1MZFFETXc4Yzk0KRRf2wbWA5l7Hh7tv8oc-wSxqi2ywMnSXVHILU3Tp4CQQsAyKxsKrX1n5Q=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/PDDU87o--VYLBWvQRFRBai1L8KPJ72ZNdsCk28YIadJ42dY8QL3MtSR2QzvSLj5eQO_VGaimM7cNW6zzRq8=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/zhbVzLuwEckie1lDOz-576ZW2s4bkMdSm0fEyzpXja1vmb3G8Tu1xFXVHCpFh-vOQQ7JjQYoo4_N8yFXMg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2Zc1Jk8TEnsGNIik16kAWZmUc4fw6q3JfH2Jx6imM_wvlS2VpyxgGy0FNfrBFSlm_Sp9EsBLT9tdlSrFcA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/gu33GCASs8V1Fuarn0wCwxdVxTyOWf1luY0boWU9ewxw7ApQHKbVvWnxw3cWjrqj_JO5IrfGVNcpTdl_=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/kJ3C38Nnfa0ZbqmuQE5Aq8uIdmm3_jZ-SdBPsr01ZBY-x5SROelYa2rOLLxk1Arh1SZl8TzjaFQ8nAlrUXY=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ZBo9RW4OsrhAdkEfUwgEQF_A5WD07xRPqgnICAIpbpBO3Ievyn9T45XeWBm4Zjp2_yVYHza3hIzsDa0Evg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/U4GfHbHsRxME0t1cvdfaCgncAZNQ-KTw933qNwHO7VEA7qaHamxIJL3PF1Aj0ROghAyHfqE9a0aFtE2YZQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/pD-rs08F_EVM19VjftNd1fC-r4BOYLfUK84TUDhatJPPEG9spP2O3gkZraceY8GBDhYTm3hS7CS2CKUksQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/D-YAklz1aUrp3NQZ1ny6vbKy7ODsSMJH_blANTZs9CzxF8_COZf4CAUCQ4mGOW1A0ykfeo4_7N82WusJWyA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/j84sAp0TphLDb6z5jp_95EHviveVr0CeH7PTJjksg_aByYMeBBTCrTITweiEmdPmxKER1Vh3v401NGLR=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Et3rJfkN352Yr3y0tgWexZo9z8Vt_O7hgvP31cpYVd5LUzpGOSVm6rX2_G4uNTQoX_IfG1pAJzxa9ThfhXc=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="17">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/JDXMT2-SUDUK9gE6AcZBHylBATtbTuwXwm5j-teRNMnSIhRy_5P6uxNIfhL1BVl66OVVdtk3fTPAUEi6hQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="18">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/bQuf88A0hO4_XQUIH3yqdv_kV-SU3DkLQUop_igvsMGwmMvuTKaPFeIMJycE0T9XCkoUlAcPCQJ0V5j4r_g=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="19">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/yQ0ljRh0ZAbAiiaTf67cYUX30UpQKTD1WpIly1lX98kkhuQ5qx9tvad5USdDMq0Qscmm3wWL2miubyaTJA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="20">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/9swSCHJ_jHdI0Wb_hNDoxUBTEXChnH192ebpgbeo5iT7iimK0sMS8Tvu818gIXYKxtQFFlrqUufl_d6NWKk=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>15330407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 09:50:37</date>
<ref>AP2-DL-LM7470</ref>
<price>120000</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Apartment</en>
</type>
<town>Elche</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>La Marina</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>1</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
Fun-tastic beach location - Luxury seafront resort in La Marina / Elche with breathtaking views, just a jump of 900 m to reach the wonderful long wide golden sandy beaches of La Marina and Guardamar. Enjoy your holidays. Pure beach life. These apartments are part of a wellkept residence with huge pool and garden area. Much thought has been given to the layout of the properties in order to make you enjoy the outdoor spaces as well as the views all around. Kitchen fittings are included and a number of extras and residence parking. 2 bed AP from only 120.000 euro up - depending on floor, size, location. You will love it. Furniture packs available. Viewings can be arranged at any time, please contact maxgoldhouse in partnership with the builder. La Marina next to Guardamar is a lovely Spanish seafront village offering really all needed amenities. Perfect place to stay here on the Southern Costa.
</en>
<de>
Stilvolle moderne Apartments in der Residenz EL PINET BEACH in La Marina/Elche - ganz nahe zum Meer - fussläufig nur ca. 900 m - zu den km-langen, feingoldenen Sandstränden von La Marina und Guardamar del Segura an der südlichen Costa Blanca. Die Wohnungen sind angelegt rund um eine herrliche grosszügige Grünanlage - natürlich mit grossem Pool. Das Design ist sehr modern, klar und hell - mit viel Sonnenlicht. Jede Einheit hat einen eigenen Parkplatz in der Anlage, es gibt die Vorinstallation von Klimaanlagen, Alarmsystemen und viele weitere Details, die aus dieser Residenz eine besondere Gelegenheit machen. Die herrliche Lage macht es zu einem der attraktivsten Orte in LA MARINA. Der Ort selbst bietet alle Versorgungseinrichtungen die man braucht - die Meereslage und die unendlichen feinen Sandstrände sind einzigartig - und umfasst über 6km Sandstrand, grosse Naturschutzgebiete / Dünenlandschaften, Pinienwaldgebiete - und die hübsche Kleinstadt selbst - nicht zu gross, nicht zu klein - genau passend für Super-Ferien in Spanien - oder einen gepflegen Altersruhesitz am Mittelmer mit allen Versorgungseinrichten. Die perfekt Lage - in moderner und guter Bauqualität. Termine können jederzeit mit maxgoldhouse als Partner des Bauträgers vereinbart werden.
</de>
<fr>
Emplacement fun-tastic près de la plage. Appartements de luxe à La Marina / Elche avec une vue fascinante, juste un saut de 900 mètres pour atteindre les longues et belles plages de sable doré de La Marina et Guardamar. Profitez de vos vacances et la vraie vie de plage. Ces appartements sont partie d'une résidence bien entretenue avec une grande piscine et un jardin. Une grande attention a été accordée à la mise en page de la propriété afin que vous puissiez profiter de l'espace extérieur et la vue. La cuisine est inclus, ainsi qu'un parking et quelques extras. Appartements avec 2 chambres commencent de seulement 120.000 euros. Les prix sont dépendent de l’étage, la grandeur, l'emplacement, etc. Vous allez aimer cet endroit. Des paquets de meubles sont disponibles. Des visites peuvent être arrangées à tout moment. Contactez maxgoldhouse en collaboration avec le constructeur. La Marina à côté de Guardamar est un beau village côtier espagnol où vous trouverez vraiment toutes les commodités nécessaires. L’endroit idéal pour séjourner sur le sud de la Costa Blanca.
</fr>
<nl>
Fun-tastische locatie dicht bij het strand. Luxueuse appartementen in La Marina / Elche met adembenemend uitzicht, slechts een sprong van 900 m om de prachtige lange, brede witte zandstranden van La Marina en Guardamar te bereiken. Geniet van uw vakantie en het pure strandleven. Deze appartementen zijn deel van een goed onderhouden residentie met een groot zwembad en een tuin. Veel aandacht is besteed aan de indeling van de woningen zodat u kan genieten van de buitenruimte en het uitzicht. Keukeninrichting is inbegrepen, evenals parkeerplaats en een aantal extra's. Appartementen met 2 slaapkamers beginnen vanaf slechts 120.000 euro. De prijzen zijn afhankelijk van verdieping, grootte, locatie, etc. Je zult het hier geweldig vinden. Meubelpakketten zijn beschikbaar. Bezichtigingen kunnen ten allen tijde geregeld worden. Neem contact op met maxgoldhouse in samenwerking met de bouwer. La Marina naast Guardamar is een prachtig Spaans kustdorpje waar je echt alle benodigde voorzieningen vind. Perfecte plek om te verblijven op de zuidelijke Costa Blanca.
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8gaHr1h3CvhI412cScGGB7P1f9y-RW6-Se_p87QGw3BnoZEdvSoUtUKt3zq3ndVe1ZyidxlpptIOYB_KCQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ewhHPMAc3BtCNewQfgR_QJDl7AXv5K_uP44q19VRreu2cWVZd9qYbtOgVj8U94yYJOwlNFk-wPKQUHEerPE=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/zZGhT0WsHf7U-R8IA3BPpQncN0MQDr4qIvvgt2NxuJp1X0kjBnCSlgRbaiMUZ3yEaSDVCwbWeDJ282pmfg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/hjxOw2d1g7MSE1tzkVkGE7Jw9s_rWsYeKfaV-Ro7ScbJD6TjKJdVWDGS4mQy5W1Jbm_nVs7Ddk_dgP1f=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/9YWnfq-Z7_ysIr61MSjSmDUzFCjd8Fl5HBSIGESvw4RQ6XbrHdZAepOg4k_qcS2TBNE1LpnAEzRnxCkiaQQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/XM5NNxBbe0D29IkJg2dluEkSu3RZO83xsjHwfPTXDeTWMIuphWqiJrekfe-Za8oO05c16a0kqgqOOqfuKw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/BPhytSJgg0-rWzSZa_5Atu_BDY2-RS-otlGNg4__9XTraUyr9rIli3CWUM0lRrD9DpBlHQeIbIYxJqWXlY0=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Uc9pMHn5Sw3bhqzkAyX6QZ--oRJZ8WIjybbRAsvy1UKoJ8bPw6al-qB1fH1ExEOPzWi6XnLtR7mNdnLa3LA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/UfwaznG6gVTy7WTUmLc8NYeUkeAW7Kz8ygroCkiKHB4e8y5dK2DXmPCn0pfsfP0Gt3dOfE7hs_T6SLedRg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/boRnuZTESXEjsgr2Ddb2R4ooDtddqALDXjDO0IPm2_KnqVkjBZ_6byQVsGfM8U1zTSOGogHRbEp86Q8bHA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/CjeX_d0AZe2tJxrkj_AHvX243yg4SGLCpgOw2XquTsQIpcKs2CeRicWYpQA8bYBz66-pm9ZUpqqdec0I=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/3kpSth75BxMrxnTUn2baJaK8-zt17FTVdhm2VBew9X7ssru45JYo36ZiyCQvbQrNnR_RM7z8q6plzn2_=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/rLD19dHlHYovgGCIqSFZIqDdi7vJ0U13sJ-m2t82GfbN26DRZF2URld3r2Rl3ZwEml7B72m7Nxals6ZG=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/EZDzyLR5QGPnI24-u46R0kCd-cLJIiwxgDpYga_rd1B_PkmjpLa8lZDvm7JEuC88TMZggRfCB-3QbuOD=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/fbYAF-yE6Vm9pENgD2PaYszEyFdqhV5tJbw7B17HvHXZhOqcG51GXJ961PYfI1dvZ0Wt6BycZpbJYHzq=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8vbMiCR-XpUuhVmo-f9LmdVQJ6muQ2b_qoRGbWBhPoCYKysanjjPtPxSnfZmsv2O3xWlDZrcM4W-t2Urug=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="17">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dXP6YEtjUgdvknyth8f1q8x7hE68XCDZ48jzPfNLGOcEMOqioEuThIRnWHxKJiL2lNk31ror5S1Khdj30qw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="18">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/p3iJz0jtTFP9TrOQ6conk60j8znmx2pFmqdoI7cm2POqq3Cih0EhpVvriVOnXnZ-YCKiNcQzpGQ-apY8bJE=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="19">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/QL0EIrnn68PgtX07r4VpoP0sJTNZEEi_NV5JEyD0qYitkxw3_Cqj4eFLCElEyFistxAgpYUa6c7sFtkI3Q=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="20">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/IKeq6sz718xcl9cyovf7eaX4NtwQFS4yUuBYHkEg32co9SKIm14oySRx0fbLwvM9T72YdgOPGG0sUrC-=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="21">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/872C6rXWMDIoql8WpjK1IdmrQZHlcGFlzEhu1vfCDLabNESt2DrDPbCft7L3iYYQNsfHIrDQLFhThZmc4w=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="22">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8-kH_C-h2uuAJo-4ZUayfaVJrexuwBnlj3dF8j0PbiUE4YfD96_im6XIdcCU_eu0LWfzWQhtujSIbjUV=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="23">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/yxpcsLuoOFRPdBut2_hmE0yD-Eu5GSQ-OrrwsUu-JyyYpS91lTZYNZwK1AbHOPqQucnduHMJKZ1cqcbo9w=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="24">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/PBLPL8yRKqcb5PbWjvgvLVi9VyEUptuMwi8bai8QpDTA8FTOC8HL0cqx3iXvcI6marf1SDUzBLFQZ92fMw0=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="25">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/PSQniyPRQjyoZh8jhjf07DOTJ5vZTdlZKr4hcgkQntyfeBNovFZgYcncTBbcMtcQ7eXL6OA-WiVKMaowD70=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="26">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/nyCExhcTJTYKd4kIFXKc9cXvx3BBrk9kaCWwl2wyJU2d5VUF-aMVTwG0a62CwcS8yBMwIC8s6uqRUVKBAg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="27">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/i1d2X13r3pNxA-Ot-0-xechqRowLeXsc7PhUV1uj3ziqpFrAGUN9HryLSEwGKHUm3mTHZBykNFJfzMp4jA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="28">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Pa5wrAff9z6mblG3932E0jHdmK1ItW7Hh9C1CFNAGD60B6ZxwNSDwoFnAg4JIduXdFP56CjetMhg02WKteo=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="29">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-thWEV3RerZaGENbxiU6pH_zjhtX8FhyJfr3Ur4iLLj9ykOJMeSWhf3F7haq1bji3_wLSFtr_IwI6v3M=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="30">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/X0v0_bPfGxbFzPgwgHL1KmXinr15nTDbrdcRe3PSpU8Exn2VU8DoDb3gRl102F-fHpRA_E8yK1qYX_99Og=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="31">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Zr2bu319oG7YM90X5ZpCpbdlJ357rlBsZdgIQWgjLHLmxsZ7iv3lKhkWSGjNXGL1p-AzaqLoar7MkY9MoQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="32">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/gfGLgWcu2sMZ7JEv84JcIM7-wOcVadALZhL-7KzpzqdTG0CsdtvtvMuHX8QfVuCr268y3tdKgaZ067lV=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="33">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/GdQPrHvYYsO_ZxvLSLD6wFNTMJQIaogxzxs_THtcuGuwO5BuxP2Bn0la-WVlI4hDMSiJftf44akTqPt7qw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="34">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/e2p1erQxeZpfZV6eIbeT27gdLnF6aFJE98HxLars-XVm1pmg2oDbTYLYmUha0My_jMA2QjN41bKUcnE1-w=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="35">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/fd3eAJhd8xQF5dXofgEJGEKx7zpGoT6SYegP_fOMDvTmOhWOoWUGWbH-LxAoyQq29ZB7GM53Qevl8p5szQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="36">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1IPwQ-e9T_21VSyC6lfxKj4jdjvfLjvKesPN3nGofrwyRF_NToecpyBFqmgklgDNHGF4Bug2XL1KTbbQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="37">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/R6S6tjLvboEHkggn89rV5BwxN8GblxfI2mb2JInz0rHLAlcoREPZ2g0VvFWA7X4sexyMtGWlcYV25ndskQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="38">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/9ytWvxnRR9BucU9_IXwuKsziW6bPgOB0-ZSPEM91u7OONcxCuQWgtYEoYHeib1jASRFR2De95i1WTvZJWA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="39">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/I_ARfYptvquAwgdEA-kDEsfm84IhKh95GaMiZpLaW4gF-y5VunE2k2tMcQnMARnYhFO2xJmfS0JoX2wMRCg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="40">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/3E9hQMxO7YufMDRbi5jgw9DWYlFus9iHRH8SEIFKbzsMSH65yIg-L_qDte42HZpWej7jZOUJQ0Zrty5gew=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="41">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/gHNIOb4TaKLv3XbdvmRuIQMKZ9946Ci8KHWfsPLWO9AvK_ZY7C0oWCTuJVTzxIIOCN54cC-cnFQ0xpaGyCg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>15360407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 20:22:54</date>
<ref>AP2-DL-PH7471</ref>
<price>123000</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Apartment</en>
</type>
<town>Pilar de la Horadada</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>Pilar de la Horadada</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>2</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
UNIQUE OFFER: GOOD QUALITY MODERN NEW BUILD APARTMENTS at only 1 km from the Medsea. The residence consists of 29 properties with communal swimming pool, there are also 3 bedroom town houses available. All apartments have 2 beds, 2 baths, and are equipped with the finest quality materials. Prices start from 123.000 euros for a groundfloor apartment, and 135.000 for a top floor. Pilar de la Horadada is a typical Spanish little town with plenty of restaurants, bars, etc. Enjoy a glass of sangria, or tinto de verano, and delicious tapas. Appointments can be made by maxgoldhouse at any time, in partnership with the builder.
</en>
<de>
Sehr schöne Neubau Anlage in Torre de la Horadada (neben Orihuela Costa - gehoert verwaltungsmäessig zur Stadt Pilar de la Horadada) - nur ca. 1 km zum Meer und den Sandstränden. Torre de la Horadada ist ein hübsches spanisches Dorf direkt am Mittelmeer mit ganz besonderem Flair. Die Kombination aus Moderne in der Residenz und historischen Elementen von Torre wird Ihnen gefallen. . . Ein Ort zum Wohlfühlen. Es gibt alles an Versorgung was mach so braucht. Ein nahezu perfektes Urlaubsziel. Wir zeigen Ihnen gerne die Residenz und die Umgebung. Torre ist nahe zu grossen Einkaufszentren, Jachthafen, diversen Golfplätzen u. a. m. - eine ideale Infrastruktur.
</de>
<fr>
Offre unique: APPARTEMENTS NEUFS MODERNES DE BONNE QUALITÉ à seulement 1 km de la mer Méditerranée. La résidence se compose de 29 maisons avec piscine commune, il y a aussi des maisons mitoyennes avec trois chambres disponibles. Tous les appartements disposent de deux chambres à coucher, deux salles de bains, et sont équipées avec les meilleurs matériaux. Les prix commencent à partir de 123.000 euros pour un appartement au rez-de-chaussée, et 135.000 pour un à l'étage supérieur. Pilar de la Horadada est une petite ville espagnole typique avec de nombreux restaurants, bars, etc. Profitez d'un verre de sangria ou tinto de verano, et de tapas délicieux. Rendez-vous pour une visite peuvent être organisé à tout moment avec Maxgoldhouse en collaboration avec le constructeur.
</fr>
<nl>
Uniek aanbod: MODERNE NIEUWBOUWAPPARTEMENTEN VAN GOEDE KWALITEIT op slechts 1 km van de Middellandse Zee. De residentie bestaat uit 29 woningen met gemeenschappelijk zwembad, er zijn ook rijhuizen met 3 slaapkamers beschikbaar. Alle appartementen hebben 2 slaapkamers, 2 badkamers, en zijn uitgerust met de beste materialen. Prijzen starten vanaf 123.000 euro voor een gelijkvloersappartement, en 135.000 voor ééntje op de bovenste verdieping. Pilar de la Horadada is een typisch Spaans stadje met veel restaurants, bars, enz. Geniet van een glas sangria, of tinto de verano, en heerlijke tapas. Afspraken voor bezichtiging kunnen te allen tijde bij Maxgoldhouse worden gemaakt in samenwerking met de bouwer.
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/AcM4LhpL1roFAWbI5CjcrxQaOAoedUZv-65gFPvWGKmDgJTZ2193C-gZNfr30lmIgTk9tWhvwcoTrrFMjg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/opOteyJbwGKUU4I1ra--JeCpRc11KVeecFcJ8tno7_0p-YfV4B9LbsC8PLtc7x-EnYXbHqrrP2H-LMlAoQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/DSLBZxKWI_t-ir0fKZPNqmSYqXNdrmgD6KzF2yaY_0Qi3Pu04fUfw76T-xPSArG9fLixJPYOQ0jphJ_xEQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/aCaN8QrkaZA6e_WpwlIBl3TcJvLa5sDdTPM5QGGE4y8eBaHOq0n1QWD-8x5hjZZrqrbh7agLkT5THC0U=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/saSTnTziKYfhVvObDV-ZLC_-Av-kMPm4skViS_tsrd8aH9UpdN6PhmW12qR3LAYERZXg5Q7VhbYjENs9=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/l9cNpK-bzJE99Y45eYgVYQz_bxjD0h3Mp6t571PcvcuDpvFx6DUjInleP7Hev06K6iLY-LBf8XQdCobMDA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/VnMG53nUOqlhNr-IITqxYX9yuMe8ZcTejLbqBBdIufAqoPltEjoNqWOM1gKwqpSx6LmanPfTBU1CiNgiAg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/VvU8REHqFEQ6-g8Bpp0t1M7wwxKPJhdc6twA2fHzbfcmeVbPDuAk2ak7pW6JBQFlFiX7oDdmHMWVDiFNRQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/EP6ghcX9SOT_ke21w8C6gN-QAZHok73SCjiCQ66MRU0FztvGkFx-sjGYh8HetCIwVe0gje9FVjc4tC5Lxg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/FJxqfK1vDMxvLI5ntdM6DPQ6JP7vdRSFvQJiR5WRHAVUjaPddNSqqmtlx1-8Smrec5VdbBTJ4aQvuHpueA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/6zWhNPMEVmiWqFJ1bgkK1W0-az_-Htuno21iqvCbyMM-seS0XSHyMMl-dSzA8ZboY-e3bAm63Wo1-kMxgI0=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/4_xE0H8iYQQN1sd9qNYijk-Gbo0DTcSiCY2Fg6yHKIB3jQsZY_sdaa7uPDEtu7hGF9jx97xOFL1zjYHIxDI=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/cu68Ejn22z4iLPYs0sx0bfs7M57jrwEdARQZt8JRtmWBDcU5FDneqmUCZYAWx4nYq0IdFplFvBUJoad_5w=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/hFpZYAAtaJ4Y79ungESksTRSzwUXS8vrH3ILmgn2ooWEIvq6nY4QxcJvDIP0t-t6eJhQs0odrrZGfn9HPw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/tcfGUunq8Cz830a5Bt-BtfeyaOE0ZwVMceGdNWUb2wt0c-n4fI1PWtlqRDRR3rW6_eNNyTFm59K4wWzX=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ubM2OxLFq3RvEc45DaoGQidmRH8TEYXMwI-jKC510AaaJnMue-lEIL9Fei2EoEwXOr4GGlc_KA2n-GTHiA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="17">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/PSSz-aMZ8bhSeekaO7s94ziwur-DGBtAxCD-YUhqg8M6I0N22PXxrksdz7bea-6HnqE6qCZOk-5ZuvHIAg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="18">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ZkQRihfUVWO9gYgR_-5E8KEfxtxpSmh5m_1A9NGh_K5sSmtCjJ-n-IzkIPqy2gOYl88cYheNVhpQViF1GA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="19">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8fISaMbfoy5lH9FzdoT2IWAvJrRPrZWrrYoUg4uV4ucvbNQpwdlmozN3wundDJ-_hTnCX-v9pBy1ANU9nuQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="20">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/AJVnpD3vAvRbv07E_VVWKjW1Y7Ivg2FC4QiOMQtblQzBCybZsjjfkizfPHPUjv3Ngo4mSY3T1YLvnFRt=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="21">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2deNe5gDwx_K2byuyqiWMMtqabeYWyfeA7jZeyqs5GiActGngH-B6lotQFqI2-9yvyPTrPbjqx79wH0gsg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="22">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/NlGLX8lMqP_qeyz4xdnJgr-jUS-vFPeSrppN_V7er-Mj2G7XNGbcezIly-n2Nn2rNM8dGXNgupkGc8O5fQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="23">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/LabCO9_fgv0zR0TXfe4eRl2qvQbzBzEpE6tRAYPO3YVH7HiXcWqLI3eT6Kl9G-iqwTgfaCFmkltzg50-=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="24">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/P8NSOfQLze5UeU0u5YhlH7WUXPFMJ-mOVWmTVxEHSVld8h2dmrtUtIoDddNner8IfbcElcnHt9Ath8dNoI4=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="25">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/FPeCpB1KL15C1rzGKn-yOonfAltttlEr7FX6IlIC0ytSpb0ls1PjnRtL-WAaQI8EZn0VlWq3LH3PEClg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="26">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/U7Yox8UOC_uB29jraix26AJbCI0TwBwsPt-N4Q-6p2gm7exH5PEBlYLfWq5-yOf9no4Jxdk4PaeXH9hbiIc=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="27">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ZLvMQxvpqvKrYwZJI3JZsQmbeoTE1xnelOmNOFqveZwaHV2SuDdyvme_SIohyb2TAYtLT_lEkhb3-PSx=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="28">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/4N3KswPLNWMvcrs_qcW46PxMtXa0Q4j9O5GVdFKaKO4AyuUQx-DPLONKRDSK5fNpaL10FThpbZQo0baxjxE=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>18050407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 10:49:05</date>
<ref>PLOT-DL-LF7654</ref>
<price>125000</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Land</en>
</type>
<town>Algorfa</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>La Finca</location_detail>
<beds>0</beds>
<baths>0</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
Spacious plot - create your private luxury villa (max. 500 sqm living area possible) - build a private pool, summer kitchen - and and and - you may have enough own ideas !! Located next to LA FINCA GOLF in the residential area of Castillo de Montemar (Algorfa townhall). A perfect place to stay for you and your family - no compromise with a builder ́s villa model - design YOUR PRIVATE VILLA - with all details you prefer exactly. Arrange your viewing with maxgoldhouse now. We can help you also in finding a serious builder in the area.
</en>
<de>DE</de>
<fr>
Terrain spacieux - construisez votre propre villa de luxe (maximum 500 m² de surface habitable possible) - construisez une piscine privée, cuisine d'été - et et et - peut-être vous avez assez d'idées de votre choix !! Situé à côté de LA FINCA GOLF dans la zone résidentielle Castillo de Montemar (municipalité d'Algorfa). Un endroit parfait pour rester pour vous et votre famille - aucune obligation de construire selon un modèle fixe d'un constructeur - concevez votre villa privée - avec tout ce que vous voulez. Organisez votre visite avec maxgoldhouse maintenant. Nous pouvons également vous aider à trouver un bon constructeur.
</fr>
<nl>
Ruim perceel - bouw uw eigen luxevilla (max. 500 m² woonoppervlak mogelijk) - bouw een privé-zwembad, zomerkeuken - en en en - misschien heeft u genoeg eigen ideeën !! Gelegen naast LA FINCA GOLF in de woonwijk Castillo de Montemar (gemeente Algorfa). Een perfecte plek om te verblijven voor u en uw gezin - geen verplichting om te bouwen volgens een vast model van een bouwer - ontwerp UW PRIVÉ-VILLA - met alles wat u wenst. Regel nu uw bezichtiging met maxgoldhouse. We kunnen u ook helpen bij het vinden van een goede bouwer.
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/OcfYBwTVJf3Vm0RxFbhdcVSFgLkGvcTbmkKPhC2Tg7aetPAJ3F9uQrg8a-YYFwfoyreClTTeFA61mKGUXg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dxI02_P10PNLxIgMsKMgSo7DdJhntJMfSudJExgr161NlnFKNsiynu-wiLhQLYVB4HAc5EFl5lltRyUI=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-ezXb8BAFRVbSAq1S_2cFPj4pCJH5tFsZ0TmT64FPQQ5qjgyiCw9VLixiugrivWobV4-LG2LxNhbq2Aan38=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/FYDOjAmQUGeqT9UZnnWEN4UC8cQSe4SvwEkqo_daHl-8TsHVoonl-W_wN4d4ECQReGya1WjdlRLY06QI3eY=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/4SzoUf56Su20oAU_WARQakdkpU6w5a_tmIk9_nrIj6-IMjCJmp0_l1GK8LWrOkj-jin85wZpN482hshlSw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dLUfQ28T80yi6OgCe6v7FXnNQTeloaYUlbTG71q_Uff47h3Q3hCY29uFbQsW3mt-UyAS6OXqfL2_Yemz=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/K0bSKRQQAn7uEuxoGR4dW55IaQmxSC9l1J9LxBhZ1stkAKa672wyjTJdJYwBKQTvP14r-sGKLcnQfZTWUA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/iUEvbCiQvW5DMyvzH2S8vCIfopwmrNvuvNPoCdQhoaPUr9oWraSuEUYCTMNL79_DDzqvYcqDU1DrzKwOyw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ObUPI0qQtqPZaLBWUZrHZCR5jYf2k8gvi6NgPFcY5vkwInWoAiPdHRA4Rod-CA1ULbqI5hPi1TjqNPUTfg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/WZi2Ja22AiRnHCR6CmWnqSBwtozl6jUr4f0n41GXhGuK2wSC9AyUzT3XYylAIZqxeJFwjp9GhLqxLzKVXYQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/EOoDdwm7b7g9lxog5_pXVR2uJUOrMB8T4pdMFE1dtsBOgyKHzBYemZXl15_PjFvbbUTG3mnERrMw8YfP=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/4Yv3cPfKrpyvOOgW1ULHj8d5gQYsR8yOwJSXidClrBDSYa1Evg1z-6bKx6urt3QrFeafdBOkVpUixINeyg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/GW5Haq92fEldlGClp6hWR7Q6fJom47k8mJumoPXp4yjBhLn-H2WSUhkFH0s0s8dlSEmogZJNXjc1JGMZAQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ehpCTO1LZHv_vaBziYnyb8TVBXq8Bh4a_17NF3xLrF0EQSAvaNZhJOcXQk0b1ujR7VTI3RkWbqQ2nohUyQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/AkUmVQS4Rdbm68OpC2CxmE6ddV9uqgrERAQvWgOyMQHKAuu2ShZ43UInUqcPdfpQ2pki5JScvHSg35W3uQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/jREA1RJmq1UJtAcF0gB1mPyCf_mLEgtdyZD7yicPm5OZYQiqdC75-8_E1lu3xp0VwMIwAQok_ZW4LG4QPsE=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="17">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/zcAnNgDmD2nFyKvOGonTJpmkfbWGmNZ1OPh44OygdSFIDFe1Mlp5Jvjs-elFSK_gJVPtAbvBPfDYEn8h=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="18">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/qrz-Gmnsls9gKhn9PqOxlLHe2b_SAKjE_yKSggBjwAJgN5PJ2Ilic7FXUyFDHM0UlPzcpxnvnYPsV3tTOA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="19">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2Yykkuk5iJ9ggiTeuraaOpJFuNU5UYJNBSqRVnSO2fdAEGMdyCZDLx3O6g4ulK1J78KCIP4baZ6jzQ87=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="20">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Yhtl8hlx8YyNJiNWfI8Hj6-P2wVQIOynd460vtGeNHtxcRzUVvq7nGCPSEyhDGQAJKcizYQuehe0CaVB=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="21">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/kXHYmJvqmD0x01RFX0fI6ouWzxohrbyXqJla7kEgV5LEHyA2wy1pKKC8M1RPtsa_vmJZbhdQOHK0DXHptQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="22">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/iulyI9oNgRzyFO63SbEhioUK_GWrsFJH7vB4o2WIBPz2IdO7Kht6duT70CtJnCuEqJXNGD5n4Si96WtQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="23">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/5IWD9x8d5P-8tnCLW5yEvK5cR1YuBZszuuo5ciyTj6RGOWqukbQ_J5Z6pDgTlEajhu2yjn9CiQfTuYFfE28=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="24">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Kcd05tLAG7yInoKxGMz_LXpiFjGPOEQMo2CpnuErppJGH2C0XMhuBwL5DNghvk7asg9hh9mzahYHprDqcw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="25">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/9wMPZGXERQclEBnJyYSaQavAU-wDjdIAJvTB3mOGYACRcEX6fYCZmeyMvIDsH-rpO1HWb0AhoPeGK60dtA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="26">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/cGqRy9ySD0fRLFpUUdVK47vxnPEyAZPuiT3DAEDVLgfUXy45x9tccCWWQIHSZkTRJd7MjrCt5ak0a-F91g=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="27">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/5lsTR4iVI1YeE0AisdhCmB8aAdG6iqw-_UyqvKJT8wUAOyU1gqHJTwtIytj7UHNs-GPONMVASc3vz-GTkw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="28">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/SSkBkUDWO4VIkHr6ePLs2DLrAyXKb_AHM_GAL7UpIOv2u_cJpiet9rnylMMTNxsrEtveuCCwjE-MJmOi5g=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>63583102736402390730407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 08:58:22</date>
<ref>SH2-DL-Alc7322b</ref>
<price>129900</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Semidetached Villa</en>
</type>
<town>Los Alcazares</town>
<province>Murcia</province>
<location_detail>Los Alcazares</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>1</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
Modern seafront semi detached villas located only ca. 800 m to sea and sandy beaches - located in Los Alcazares/Mar Menor - close to all amenities in a short walking distance. This is your dream location near the sea. Available are some semi detached villas with terrace and garden - and a private pool as an option. Enjoy your glass of wine or beer (or even Whiskey) after a wonderful beach walk along the medsea shore. These modern new build villas are pre-installed for A/C and tv and phone and open for your private furniture pack which we have to offer from renowned furniture suppliers. Modern style well priced and full service included. Los Alcazares is near several golf courses, huge shopping malls and more along the Mar Menor. Ask also for some detached villas in this residence / plots of 350 sqm
</en>
<de>
In Los Alcazares am Mar Menor werden diese modernen hübschen DHH / Doppelhaushälften gebaut -zusammen mit einigen freistehenden Villen. Es ist ein idealer Standort - nur ca. 800 m zum Meer - Alcazares ist ein nettes kleines spanisches Mittelmeerstädtchen und hat absolut alles was man braucht an Versorgungseinrichtungen. Ein idealer Platz zum Leben - oder nur zum Urlauben. . . Alcazares ist nahe zu vielen Golfplätzen, grossen Einkaufszentren und bietet ein sehr gepflegtes Ambiente mit spanischem Flair. Besichtigungen können jderzeit mit maxgoldhouse als Partner für diesen Bauträger vereinbart werden.
</de>
<fr>
Serena Garden Los Alcazares, Mar Menor. Modernes villas mitoyennes situés à environ 800 m de la mer, les plages de sable fin et à proximité de toutes les commodités. Il s’agit de villas mitoyennes avec terrasse et jardin. Une piscine privée est facultative. Ces nouvelles villas modernes ont pré-installation pour la climatisation (chaude / froide), TV et téléphone. Nous pouvons également offrir des paquets de meubles de fournisseurs réputés, de style moderne à un prix compétitif. Los Alcazares est proche de plusieurs terrains de golf, les grands centres commerciaux et à proximité de la Mar Menor. Dans ce complexe, il y a également un certain nombre de villas individuelles avec un terrain de 350 m² disponibles.
</fr>
<nl>
Serena Garden Los Alcazares, Mar Menor. Modern half-vrijstaande villa’s op ca. 800 m van de zee, zandstranden en dicht bij alle voorzieningen. Het gaat om half-vrijstaande villa's met terras en tuin. Een privé-zwembad is optioneel. Deze moderne nieuwbouwvilla's hebben pré-installatie voor airco (warm/koud), tv en telefoon. We kunnen u ook meubelpakketten aanbieden van gerenommeerde meubelleveranciers, moderne stijl voor een scherpe prijs. Los Alcazares ligt dicht bij diverse golfbanen, grote winkelcentra en vlak bij de Mar Menor. In dit complex zijn ook een aantal vrijstaande villa's beschikbaar met een grondstuk van 350 m².
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-hepcUyJqjmc/WWS0v35CnrI/AAAAAAAAPoE/khRnpCmt50AlwS_I94xPmAUPAovi1ji7ACHMYBhgL/s640/2c.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-cb4J9T1yQqQ/WWS0v-uBUOI/AAAAAAAAPoE/ltMSYGbYjOs3SlwuOveVe2nf-hoW9dB3gCHMYBhgL/s640/1a.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-vXfZiOWPa50/WWS0v1BH0VI/AAAAAAAAPoE/K0dkEC9GwM42QQbchlaR-l0cL8VdWc_MQCHMYBhgL/s640/2.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-_hzqaVBZO-g/WWS0v24o2xI/AAAAAAAAPoE/vSR8vSosWAoeYsdumrwYtwDZXLmEwvjmACHMYBhgL/s640/2b.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-y9KJWvQPtTM/WWS0v65DZoI/AAAAAAAAPoE/tymdJyAVSig-l3GunsqHE5PToVlaCIrmwCHMYBhgL/s640/3a.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-BIPy8Bdvt3E/WWS0vxvPN8I/AAAAAAAAPoE/EMFeySCvCMc9oicnryNw_LZjgYqec1x2gCHMYBhgL/s640/3b.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-XuQhgjxhZ9s/WWS0v6LPslI/AAAAAAAAPoE/SOpDXJJmONocEQzwQL9fdQz6ZYCf_GEpgCHMYBhgL/s640/3c.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-S3B60lK_f00/WWS0v8oxLBI/AAAAAAAAPoE/aVVs2zFhhLka0QngH1GQzy5WBPgMDfw8QCHMYBhgL/s640/3.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-4QAlgcR5cew/WWS0v6i6VII/AAAAAAAAPoE/7CWidHwNmF09WHUGKlAOrt826iqazAfeACHMYBhgL/s640/3d.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-1qH-Mc_ScCY/WWS0v8BOX_I/AAAAAAAAPoE/jG4GY7Y1V2UAJ6rmiOjhvJqhunmfPuA1QCHMYBhgL/s640/3f.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-6gAJIxhrtgk/WWS0vz-ZPBI/AAAAAAAAPoE/yUzcKn64oJ4Xs4NkCgFwrdq9GZpxzqWqQCHMYBhgL/s640/4a.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-vRX0DKTnVl4/WWS0v18Y2AI/AAAAAAAAPoE/7KHNmuxxoQkaGeAuj0Gjcn13EzQBFjRuACHMYBhgL/s640/4b.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-8oqzjw-E_TI/WWS0vxHpyJI/AAAAAAAAPoE/SIChj6fy_-Umy8k0wgYPWygzfC7MZQxtgCHMYBhgL/s640/4c.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-NXZBFagPUDc/WWS0v74XrKI/AAAAAAAAPoE/DezbUC_Bw-wezIy5ds2sK868hp_y5dvVwCHMYBhgL/s640/4d.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-nzmxEQRMDy0/WWS0vwRtZpI/AAAAAAAAPoE/_ofBP5YTtqYF467bxYlXr4nom5xkLZomACHMYBhgL/s640/1b.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>16180407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 15:12:05</date>
<ref>AP2-DL-PH7550</ref>
<price>133900</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Apartment</en>
</type>
<town>Pilar de la Horadada</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>Pilar de la Horadada</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>2</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
Modern attractive holiday resort apartments in Pilar de la Horadada (next to Torre de la Horadada and Orihuela Costa) by the sea in a wonderful residential development. All apartments have underground parking and benefit from an excellent Southern orientation with nice views to swimming pools and gardens. The ground floor apartments include a spacious garden and the top floor AP include a huge roof terrace. Kitchen units are included as are a number of extras. The really lovely Spanish seafront village Torre de la Horadada (part of Pilar d.l.H.) offers all you may need, sea and beaches, the marina, shopping centres, restaurants and bistros, water sports, and last but not least several golf courses nearby. You can arrange a full viewing with maxgoldhouse.
</en>
<de>
Sehr schöne Neubau Anlage im RETRO STYLE in Pilar de la Horadada (direkt neben Orihuela Costa) - nur ca. 2 km zum Meer und den Sandstränden von Torre de la Horadada ist ein hübsches spanisches Dorf direkt am Mittelmeer mit ganz besonderem Flair. Die Kombination aus Moderne in der Residenz und historischen Elementen von Torre wird Ihnen gefallen. . . Ein Ort zum Wohlfühlen. Es gibt alles an Versorgung was mach so braucht. Ein nahezu perfektes Urlaubsziel. Wir zeigen Ihnen gerne die Residenz und die Umgebung. Torre ist nahe zu grossen Einkaufszentren, Jachthafen, diversen Golfplätzen u. a. m. - eine ideale Infrastruktur.
</de>
<fr>
Appartements de vacances modernes et attrayants dans une belle résidence près de la mer à Pilar de la Horadada (à côté de Torre de la Horadada et Orihuela Costa). Tous les appartements disposent d'un parking souterrain et sont exposés plein sud avec de belles vues sur les piscines et les jardins communaux. Les appartements au rez-de-chaussée ont un grand jardin et les appartements à l'étage supérieur ont une grande terrasse sur le toit (solarium). La cuisine complète est incluse, ainsi qu'un certain nombre d'extras. Le magnifique village côtier espagnol de Torre de la Horadada (partie de Pilar de la Horadada) vous offre tout ce dont vous avez besoin: mer et plage, port de plaisance, centres commerciaux, restaurants et bistrots, sports nautiques, sans oublier plusieurs parcours de golf. Vous pouvez organiser une visite avec l'équipe Maxgoldhouse.
</fr>
<nl>
Moderne, aantrekkelijke vakantie-appartementen in een prachtige residentie vlakbij zee in Pilar de la Horadada (naast Torre de la Horadada en Orihuela Costa). Alle appartementen hebben een ondergrondse parkeergarage en liggen op het zuiden met mooi uitzicht op de gemeenschappelijke zwembaden en tuinen. De appartementen op de begane grond beschikken over een ruime tuin en de appartementen op de bovenverdieping hebben een groot dakterras (solarium). De volledige keuken is inbegrepen, evenals een aantal extra's. Het prachtige Spaanse kustdorp Torre de la Horadada (deel van Pilar de la Horadada) biedt u alles wat u nodig heeft: zee en strand, de jachthaven, winkelcentra, restaurants en bistro's, watersporten en niet te vergeten een aantal golfbanen in de buurt. U kunt een bezichtiging regelen met het Maxgoldhouse team.
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/gO9vgW53UiroJF0yPTkoWaV_-0vVr1Q3AGoXGie1O3_7huNfeIYjhGCtK514NxYLYafADAWEuxYtXW-EmA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/UZ7jcK5CxTWWn7nqQdB4gt0lp8Y9j57FTSX7H8fdlg0ldJexunwyB-zOI4aN1CXh4_Jsu-YvaT0qjbkagQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/q1cRLBFj5suU3lqrPhElwFcmE2n3lW41PFKmRyjBsJcLHpSANI1I-0Kn3vuvrMrnj1TC_0dk1pk3SIg--h8=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2HG3caNTSj9ctWdBVbP15z-O0uNkXUeZC_tZw8aI6vjuHY1h5uikh30-c8ZUBv4OKmB6IsGzWuPnNEHE4w=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/m4YylT8vFLMMsG-2pnzUEOXdhwUB9coVsAVYg9FdgTisuvaECXqbDKm1tgyRZvmd9psN2Tft_uli00gVS3I=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/a76ClcuiaICf_DkkOIXDFwAHfY85i00796kDsK7iHcQYATQJXCk_2epXAJ7Eom48ikFWLU9XCt8YhUkGTZE=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/4k7lFT4dtQeWFhCnK77Qhe50RlEj_IsyeDkkKF5g93XYunVAK7wGhkIzrvBSlVx6SsM-h8Csc-apijPiRA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/74I0vddJaL6fUe1It8CmuljFEjwi6qRf09RR15C966m9QrI37WjmHpYBc7y2ZRtMeOg1H9eZAm6bUpkpbw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/5wZO8SFnqFseF5mzS7APpuvPtPyxu9twqEvHU7osHyqFMXgYRHsOlxYASIn8wXr8MRR3W5HTUcgZCp95=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Ke4CaLny1SpnqY9MddHnJL9CvhmliIs9ZA9HqfN0nHdpaKkiXG8UKLYl0Sd8pmtniEmxXQp_zV0ROUgXJQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/LGlNHoRpoHPWdBZj7HVc3GbUh1wELlL8fcCO1EtP8dloUDrLv1PAgzG4nDqi3SX140YNGgq5oj0huB4bgg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/iw16_-Pduo5uK-dFZa16bBirksOM0_yDML1QcMx2Gsys0tMEgAotacE_R0FsNdlUKdKOIKEiBoDmxIOlecs=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/RzLrRZK5pLa52UjtiJVBftZnEV-U6QLg5XGueJZs8GQnBPvnvrNg-ZjVlf8bh8kgmmlKS9HbdDnv1CdT=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/zSot2BrS11QXTn-yiFEH-YNlkICHTKxCsLV8ByQnAO80nYetsEL7qCxhjlgMJ4Q8jjMux8y3fZDRK5ok=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/VW6Yfe3aXyBwTWdrq9Lrif7pvyMmRdyjVny7lzElF6LquX_pf2d1prwkimb_coaoa-U0MNvvqnWKcHHE=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>15460407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 15:39:42</date>
<ref>DH2-DL-PH7490</ref>
<price>181900</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Detached Villa</en>
</type>
<town>Pilar de la Horadada</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>Pilar de la Horadada</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>2</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
Unique golf and sea location : Modern stylish detached 2bed Villas in Pliar de la Horadada just 7 kms to sea and sandy beaches of the lovely Spanish village Torre de la Horadada - next to Orihuela Costa - close to all amenities in a short and comfortable distance. Available are some detached villas in 3 diff. Models - with terrace / garden / roof terrace - highest standards - ask also for 3bed options. These modern new build villas are pre-installed for A/C and heating and tv and phone and ready for your choice of furniture pack which we have to offer from renowned furniture suppliers. Modern style - well priced - and full service included. The residence is in the middle of a unique lovely golf course - the Pilar town has all you may need and is close to some huge shopping malls – and more gold courses along the southern Costa. Arrange now your personal viewing appointment with maxgoldhouse in partnership with the builders.
</en>
<de>
Einzigartige Lage in der Nähe des Golfs und des Meeres in Pilar de la Horadada: Moderne stilvolle Villen mit 2 Schlafzimmern in einem Golfresort und nur 7 km vom Meer und den Sandstränden des schönen spanischen Dorfes Torre de la Horadada, neben Orihuela Costa. Alle Einrichtungen sind in kurzer Entfernung. Zur Verfügung stehen einige freistehende Villen in 3 verschiedenen Modellen. Sie haben eine Terrasse / Garten / Dachterrasse und sind nach höchsten Standards gebaut. Es gibt auch einige Villen mit 3 Schlafzimmern. Diese modernen, neu gebauten Villen verfügen über eine Vorinstallation für Klimaanlage und Heizung, TV und Telefon. Wir können Ihnen auch ein eigenes Möbelpaket anbieten, das wir von namhaften Möbelherstellern anbieten können. Moderner Stil - preisgünstig - und voller Service inklusive. Was will man mehr? Die Residenz befindet sich inmitten eines einzigartigen, wunderschönen Golfplatzes - die Stadt Pilar hat alles, was Sie brauchen, und liegt in der Nähe einiger großer Einkaufszentren und weiterer Golfplätze an der südlichen Costa. Vereinbaren Sie jetzt Ihren persönlichen Termin mit maxgoldhouse in Zusammenarbeit mit den Bauherren.
</de>
<fr>
Endroit unique proche des courts de golf et de la mer à Pilar de la Horadada: villas modernes et élégantes avec 2 chambres sur un golf resort et à seulement 7 km de la mer et des plages de sable fin du charmant village espagnol de Torre de la Horadada, à côté de Orihuela Costa. Toutes les commodités sont dans une courte distance. Disponibles sont quelques villas détachées dans 3 modèles différents. Elles ont terrace, jardin, toit-terrace, et sont construites selon les plus hautes normes. Ces nouveaux villas modernes sont pré-installés pour A / C et du chauffage, de la télévision et le téléphone. Nous pouvons vous offrir aussi votre propre paquet de meubles de fournisseurs renommés. Style moderne - bon prix - et un service complet inclus. Que plus vous voulez? La résidence est située au milieu d'un parcours de golf belle unique - la ville de Pilar a tout ce que vous avez besoin et est proche de quelques grands centres commerciaux et terrains de golf le long de la Costa sud. Organisez votre rendez-vous personnel avec maxgoldhouse maintenant en collaboration avec les constructeurs.
</fr>
<nl>
Unieke locatie vlak bij de golf en de zee in Pilar de la Horadada: Moderne stijlvolle villa’s met 2 slaapkamers op een golf resort en op slechts 7 km van de zee en de zandstranden van het prachtige Spaanse dorp Torre de la Horadada, naast Orihuela Costa. Alle voorzieningen liggen op een korte afstand. Beschikbaar zijn enkele vrijstaande villa’s in 3 verschillende modellen. Ze hebben een terras / tuin / dakterras, en zijn gebouwd volgens de hoogste normen. Er zijn ook enkele villa’s met 3 slaapkamers beschikbaar. Deze moderne nieuwbouwvilla’s hebben pre-installatie voor air conditioning en verwarming, tv en telefoon. We kunnen ook zorgen voor uw eigen meubelpakket dat we van bekende meubelleveranciers kunnen aanbieden. Moderne stijl - goed geprijsd - en volledige service inbegrepen. Wat wil u nog meer? De residentie ligt midden in een unieke mooie golfbaan - de stad Pilar heeft alles wat je nodig hebt en ligt dicht bij een aantal grote winkelcentra en meer golfbanen langs de zuidelijke Costa. Regel nu uw persoonlijke afspraak met maxgoldhouse in samenwerking met de bouwers.
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dCUJc0sggwE-ktanS76qynpS8wKY5pZf2tt0CNGajVW1NvXL1veOE7lYPZWmZLtmzbg4dmTqjO6zsO0xxQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/iDiqtxLKQ_fG5fpMryD3diKEatPkdwNfAV3f6gaTHsbEBpobj-SdE1qRXPynCE1mKJTBtw1Z0m5Wem5zyrE=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/uylOpcFpN6jZIKWKEOe5QnFMpHNwRMtk-6MrDUUu8Ixxh5yCV4cBMr88KEiMl0QWTD80fj2U0TGWmdJcNlY=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/S2bb7wPOPwgYZDWpEEIuTN9Laj-_8STOxAlZU_AYo_a2YNe4NAfOgCBG7UHIuBTQhQn3d7SfCppXrReBKg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Bvz8ZOyEUS4O9Bk14wPzmc1ko2taXcMIgogoRyvlIKW52ZkBY85CaSzh-PrpNkvlU_hawtATNLIaIl0lWg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1byz5-4qXu4r2sv-Ia9RVsKIzc3Tl1DVQBSeW0Y3oQxPQ33xUE2-DrPoRiPese2MBdYQDsUtNlvQZ9xKEA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/EvbWqAOnO82hpxo-qsxJ99LwC59_dxjHrgqkp0eoFmdZB5ZgTNjkbXHmAUUjYQKLAdmhjC_h8nmscGQtmA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/qBEtvUu8T_Mv6Ae6d806W4kdye3Rrk94CGBLx7iC4PM5GUUXx2NxjGeDq5r9nmSTlgscbkgMiEocAE4cRw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/CJ2AZhVXwZ2Cb2IfPKDK8AkiMPAaWGIqn8wKfBDKxc2sbIkTXeOYDj82mANfw29ttpH8IB_8oycUFDxzOA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/osjqhZHXUbR_tscuVlTMcEKyBRM9yGLlgyOqNgC9NEfcF49Qi760Xsl4_Q7jz2tXueT9RVtIjw-2-xYqPA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/eWWQqdtw5fjLkMP5_zHCTkZ8pXgLZU3reBJTnIzJOuF4komfJE_vp5yoUgw98Dtv6OhpbAcPpt5jVHW6Gg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/y7WZ1qd8KyZreJJGk_o7I04NHV9FswPVth5pXrrbK9BlcgSwh1vHQLlXwPGb8sc5IDgMeoGkp7DDBp8Liw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/LSOBNvE4aU3-5gItUJtF06ZbHRYtiGYa9TvD_FAVzQOJ6rqxanlJnzUowjXGWAXjS41r1ZlsCHuwJMX1=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/hM3hGDY5qjWW0ideiH2ALhl9lwFS6zADs3L4vtomDyB20Ji7z76VQ-lvZfyoAg-_0lETEYnZoj8zAY_n9A=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/qLtBiGiAjXiip1_7LAAX8SCM4i99qhTulWkmvRsaiIPcCzlSbswfQe7_2IjMLPMRGf6IcXVPSq3CuSMrVUM=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/HwuBqlgmeGKv0B25ft-JwUhZJRbnmehQzEMynvWHWwj-zK4sBF1ZN0AQURyi9ziMH1fuBMgThSncSb8ZAQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="17">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/JrufIRk8Mhtl_nht0Rk0yoDrklLNMb0iQNcje7dRAxB_4ZB6_4H4kCdYpaBmAoA4vAcqWI4v2csLKtzb=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="18">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/BeRhkZfJ1jw0yZIuoVbmYem9dVrNpS4P_E7pbPATSP4Rt2-Mc9YBacJwWs7a4KUGhvPlzlTIhM_c1LcOjg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>15250407</id>
<date>2018-07-04 15:38:10</date>
<ref>AP2-DL-3-DL-V7141</ref>
<price>182000</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Apartment</en>
</type>
<town>Orihuela Costa</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>Villamartin Golf</location_detail>
<beds>2</beds>
<baths>2</baths>
<pool>1</pool>
<url/>
<desc>
<en>
LUXURY MODERN SOUTH FACING SEA VIEW RESIDENCE in the famous Villamartin/Los Dolses area located just a short walking distance from all needed amenities and close to 4 international golf courses and only 1.5 kms to sea and beaches. The residence has 3 communal pools. One pool is covered and heated aloowing all year round swimming. The Villamartin area offers large shopping centres, lots of restaurants and is close to sea and beaches with all kinds of watersports. These stylish apartments with various floor plans are equipped to really high standards with walk-in showers, wardrobes in the bedrooms, fully glazed terrace doors, pre-installation for air conditioning hot/cold and TV, modern kitchen furniture and white goods included and more. The prices for the modern luxury apartments on diff. floors start from 182.000 euro - depending on size, bedrooms, views and location. Included in the sales price are underground garage parking and storage rooms. Ask for all details. Viewings at any time.
</en>
<de>
Wunderschöne Neubau-Residenzanlage mit grossen Pool- und Gartenanlagen - gelegen in Villamartin / Los Dolses - zum Meer in La Zenia nur ca. 4-6 Minuten per Auto - oder 10 Minuten mit dem Fahrrad. Moderne und excellente Ausführung - top Qualitäten in jedem Detail, eine sehr besondere Wohnresidenz. Sie können noch Änderungswünsche äussern für einige Detailsausführungen, je nach Fertigstellungstermin. Die erste Einheit ist fertiggestellt - Sie können also exakt sehen, wie gebaut wurde / wird - kein Kauf ab Plan - sondern am konkreten Beispiel zu prüfen. Es gibt noch ein paar wenige Resteinheiten im ersten Wohnteil. Jeweils mit TG und Fahrstuhl, herrlichen Meerblicken - und fussläufig zu allen Versorgungseinrichten. Auch zum grossen ZENIA BOULEVARD Shopping Center sind es nur 10 Minuten zu Fuss - für uns eine der besten modernen Wohnresidenzen in Orihuela Costa.
</de>
<fr>
LUXUEUSES ET MODERNES APARTEMENTS, orientés au SUD et avec VUE sur la MER dans la célèbre Villamartin / Los Dolses, situés à seulement une courte distance de marche de toutes les commodités nécessaires et à proximité de 4 terrains de golf internationaux et à seulement 1,5 km de la mer et des plages. La résidence dispose de 3 piscines communales, d’où une est couverte et chauffée permettant à nager toute l'année. Villamartin vous offre de grands centres commerciaux, de nombreux restaurants et est proche de la mer et des plages avec toutes sortes de sports nautiques. Ces appartements élégants et spacieux avec différents plans d'étage sont équipés aux normes très élevées avec douches italiennes, placards dans les chambres, portes de terrasse entièrement vitrées, pré-installation pour la climatisation chaud / froid et la télévision, des meubles de cuisine moderne. Les appareils électriques sont inclus dans le prix. Les prix pour ces appartements de luxe modernes commencent à partir de € 182 000, dépendant de la grandeur, le nombre de chambres, l’étage, etc. Inclus dans le prix de vente sont stationnement de garage et de stockage souterrains. Demandez tous les détails, s.v.p. Tour à tout moment.
</fr>
<nl>
Luxueuze, moderne appartementen met ZEEZICHT en ZUIDGERICHT in het bekende Villamartin / Los Dolses, gelegen op slechts een korte loopafstand van alle benodigde voorzieningen, dicht bij 4 internationale golfbanen en op slechts 1,5 km van zee en de stranden. De residentie heeft 3 zwembaden, waarvan één overdekt en verwarmd zodat je het hele jaar door kan zwemmen. Villamartin biedt grote winkelcentra, veel restaurants en ligt dicht bij de zee en de stranden met allerlei watersporten. Deze stijlvolle en ruime appartementen met diverse grondplannen zijn uitgerust volgens de hoogste normen met walk-in douches, kasten in de slaapkamers, volledig glazen terrasdeuren, pre-installatie voor airconditioning warm / koud en TV, moderne keuken, enz. Elektrische toestellen zijn inbegrepen in de prijs. De prijzen voor deze moderne, luxe- appartementen beginnen vanaf € 182 000, en zijn afhankelijk van de grootte, aantal slaapkamers, verdieping, enz. Inbegrepen in de prijs zijn een ondergrondse parkeergarage en berging. Vraag gerust voor alle details. Bezichtigingen op elk gewenst moment.
</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/E7DO8hMWED0-jDJcVGfwp08iSltRf552syTgudIVIzxAmiHABPezJmnpGZ60sH18ryQcNeAU4ys40zSR=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="2">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/c9UymDdKtyuGqoW_j7c5_woNVrFSaChs-Py4HVxflLIU9dP7nsPMkiO7GTQjaXnQSrTqEhqxdDSJGOfgXQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="3">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/pfEhA6JWULQYlFVZk8lEXdi37sd71CErZkCjxVS71nsZjD93A-lzcFx72R5m6lqxLJHZ4v0Tjaj8eiSE=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="4">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/IHReL5WkirynCAZQt_4NzPeOcTEZ7FcJgaJ469pXW1ERYGxjaoyKh_jS2qEyqzVCf_NzL_GvTKKZgc-Fjw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="5">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/gzM3FHhAtQRvMCevpRt6huTLXdHDGwuDTvy0AjuU9Kozw7smaMkpc8WLZmPHYFefOp4nx_eWHEmdm_V-3A=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="6">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/rJGPWVRSNKAPyziskfxocpXvTO-6SHBPD8yDzpiSX5zVVAEUAq1fqbAzWbAVqNrCOK6Auzg6d9ZNpy_8xg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="7">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/noODj9tRLLjff9x4MERhP8QI-On3LyZjW9RArKGgEenz--QcuIg7QlCioQ8XTVRru9NO_ZkWOUlnyPho=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="8">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/FTgBWMqNfa76iDk4IIFk_RuwjB4VpAOIzkyy3qBd9jKo4VBWcvX6unoixbwpxxAzSK5bqKj4Mk61kGfqog=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="9">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/rVWk5OsrgYYS_kzAvPa6Bb375i397NJWNfDk4WDgkYHZxVJSWtKsmAB2m_2hnYvxI_IkRhGhEJxF8VWWP5c=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="10">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/bM-aDnXnIUoN-P8bh9pTTvywPaNWScZnx5iyzvjhjROVI0LZWqeF56nQxyT_SYdVK1-Tr0A0-mROBXqv=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="11">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/gF56qoo7Wql3HRlF8iwR04v1277jMNWZxqaUanluGz8m9evyDcjGBbuI7_Ak9kxTCuGCyBLCziIG5lokCQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="12">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1jGwpgXXv1OhIYf8qSMdi8Nqy7CB88ij-x8aGVLKgWDdNnYCgOlvW-973mLiUJ3KPPJqH0m4VFP5CPo58BE=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="13">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/nv5ls89YFhfxdmF-IhtP94nStIOtysrttVFRv-ektwQk_KNIuLFB13gJuN6u2Uw3kfY0VVcMnS6l60wQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="14">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/AOf8xbgy4RWWCefjKnjcjVaVdZIiwZP41D5TJ9LB5vU2JviuUWDbsE8wqhukQulFePcMGOgWG_JcBvHr7g=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="15">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dbmwYon8SyfCEb_LtvWTRWhtFF_CudYlyKeQIto_8UYisf7CrLEd9zA0f1rkRXJ6Kx9NqIutJWXahDppoCo=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="16">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/VZR9WNp8jkTiDQ3cP0tl_ZIMH6Zse7tco2pyF3KHHxSixle-_jThiP-1ULC2M3VfxyJjsSNuice-jpx-=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="17">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/C25M3oXU8IpRdHVfaOHwVJ821M4UZBOJxFcwCyBwRZ0d1f9xAHL4o_iTjePUTm2fwZXWt6sLCW0DrjD09w=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="18">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/XsZmQQ4huI77GAQNnoX5Py6R6xZYRx3O1_n1m9fC72mgSIc-JviRz4YjqWQB7AFfKWX9DMIBdPbNrVqEnA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="19">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/uRQXD3P2LQSjqZlYXkd14CNIZ3UqW1GJqetzYgv2FYLDZDciMnr64UtHM-L_CjmfU-OcojLsFqGraAAIzw=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="20">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/m2X0tcxIJw5dDLkCgByGWY4i7hnV7fb9ZRaHYhMlI_co0MvL8Sb22FZSU91hVb3Wu4zx1DVk8Og7mpso1l0=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="21">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/4nt-OJzeuTYCW-CpK_9jFR9fhjHkTfQvaxk4TrfeEJvofiesVajesbivPjJUkoRy36WbHuAgdbefhc_tAb4=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="22">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8KJB4V_8smTFK8kiQZk0IIFM8-X93yG8EtW6AKo4cViJIhPotDGIKafThG4688mSxgFbWDLUmZWot7cNxls=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="23">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/DcwL1wAcLCrGlXldECkd0aU49TrhW9Fur9tgi_ps3KmJbx38dYCfrsBZNstpiGVwWTJdt0LJCfUGWJBc=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="24">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/i8-VDqOA3fxYHKU_NaGHALN7FyJwVUCqJpz5kjoGd5Lunaw8OeEg_qWggsb4rskgDsc79hVxta0ytNMe=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="25">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/jFz1ps5UxLej2IlTtBlBU0mOvcfUEKm_pHNxO90mUtIr333VmZIImWX1x1gpuyRiN4fn-Lt1CvLzkGXhHA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="26">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/jgQiu0BvNOMDBgbbpuniNdCNxvfG9Wgbq9HLNa0abdg7128Me32ZkxnwedwvOeAZ6ooL3JQDLMDkDV9j=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="27">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/gqu74dXTOLHMkdnwXnvUHd_ABX0dD344y-MuvEY47BwS1JgVwYHvWlRjX0jdXVw113AIminZpSPyzVQe=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="28">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/DktaH668uthSzwtOdLY8cWyaVj8DCerTq2QMIORbX09toIR7S1vOgb75tI4wX73EHZsD5PijDt0XZnOu=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="29">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8c3x3-LuYYDpNPkw2lHBmqXaet3o3xlaHn_dwIw9DXIf4tz--hgDP6mXsREM0k0aOogTUm0Ey8IdwsPJPg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="30">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/pskK3ELWwR40FOCHeKZd0jZJT6dpnS4F0ZR95ENEMdSSstjXQruRv0SZBH1FD3RCcGS31QglUDxx-BtM3w=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="31">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/RE-Ne_AvgN4h2prlD81wk3yy6kM2G6nOChUjnO2RdrVJNH-gnGFVVURaQjvajZrmhXjMogy2mzFxxTPszK4=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="32">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/CK83_2_o2DI_1CkR8sznA2ZHkxQX-eVrs0AGRft6S_5admdvvEO0qsxh4Ok9T9B4YJlmsXWfWi8KJ3jOWQ=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="33">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/C0rvLHeEwf69Kh49SbSYI08QxOS4plKM4qrTLECzjIOOP5g6Z3vymWjChxks_rOfhReoempXGaLGlmt3VA=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="34">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/rs7d8DoYYaCmgJEkPZl7NQ0ls9CRS4TXTbtFJ0BQ2uCvkU-ZFsj8Ru7ZpThKgteLme2h5qdyeb24ZCTd=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
<image id="35">
<url>
http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/vq8INakmWR1o5OxI--5mE1nhfmJ4DzbKe9c2Y1CRUap5MqS45mXdp71rSwuU2LuwCcMxvI4OvD_SKaXBDg=s640-rj-e30-v2?.jpg
</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
<property>
<id>15070718</id>
<date>2018-07-03 11:21:18</date>
<ref>TH4-TB001DL</ref>
<price>219997</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Townhouse</en>
</type>
<town>Tibi</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>Tibi</location_detail>
<beds>4</beds>
<baths>3</baths>
<pool>0</pool>
<url>https://www.maxgoldhouse.com/4-bed-Townhouse-in-Tibi-1507.html</url>
<desc>
<en>Duplex Townhouse in authentic rural village (Tibi, Alicante). The house offers 4 bedrooms all with floor to ceiling built in wardrobes, 3 bathrooms (master is en-suite), internal laundry patio, large pantry, separate kitchen with dining table, lounge dining room, large entrance terrace overlooking the park, large upstairs balcony terrace with wide mountain views &amp; underground garage parking with store room.   Broadband Internet is available as well as the free Wi-Fi offered by the library 2 minutes walk away. Tibi is a quiet authentic living village community about 20 minutes inland from the coast up in the mountains.   Tibi is an excellent choice for families with children or for retired people who want to live away from the busy life of the coast or the city but with all the facilities for modern living close at hand. Hidden but not isolated, Tibi has a new library with free Wi-Fi, a new indoor market, a new medical centre and a new sports centre with swimming pool. Tibi is popular with cyclists and walkers who enjoy the many trails in the area. The Maigmo National Park is within Tibi's borders. Tibi is a great place from which you can explore the local towns and villages of the area. The village is well communicated with Alicante City, Alicante Airport &amp; the coast.. The village Sports Centre offers, tennis, five a side, basketball, Valencian hand ball court and swimming pool. The village centre is family friendly with outdoor theatre/cinema and bars with shady terraces. Outdoor market twice a week and new indoor market. Shops 6 days a week. There are many neighbouring towns and villages within 10-20 minutes away with market days &amp; fiestas. Wonderful place</en>
<de>Duplex-Reihenhaus in der ländlichen Gemeinde Tibi, in Alicante. Das Haus verfügt über vier Schlafzimmer, jeweils mit Einbauschränken vom Boden bis zur Decke, 3 Bäder (Master en-suite), Waschraum, separate Küche mit Esstisch und großem Hauswirtschaftsraum, Wohn- / Esszimmer, große Terrasse mit Blick auf den Park, große Terrasse auf der obersten Etage mit Panoramablick auf die Berge und eine Tiefgarage mit Abstellraum. Breitband-Internet ist verfügbar, sowie kostenloses WLAN, die Sie die Bibliothek bieten (2 Minuten zu Fuß). Tibi ist ein ruhiges, authentisches Dorf, etwa 20 Minuten von der Küste entfernt. Tibi ist eine ausgezeichnete Wahl für Familien mit Kindern oder für Rentner, die weg von der Hektik der Küste oder der Stadt bekommen wollen, aber mit allen Annehmlichkeiten für modernes Wohnen in der Nähe. Versteckt, aber nicht isoliert. Tibi hat eine neue Bibliothek mit kostenfreiem WLAN in einem neuen Markt, ein neues medizinisches Zentrum und ein neues Sportzentrum mit Schwimmbad. Tibi ist beliebt bei Radfahrern und Wanderer, die die vielen Wanderwege in der Umgebung. Der Maigmo Nationalpark liegt innerhalb der Grenzen von Tibi. Tibi ist ein großartiger Ort, um die lokalen Städte und Dörfer der Gegend zu erkunden. Das Dorf ist leicht von Alicante, Flughafen Alicante und der Küste. Das Sportcenter können Sie Tennis, Basketball, Handball und Schwimmen Valencia spielen. Das Dorfzentrum ist familienfreundlich mit Außen Theater / Kino sowie Bars mit schattigen Terrassen. Zweimal in der Woche gibt es einen Markt unter freiem Himmel, und es gibt auch eine neue Indoor-Markt. Die Geschäfte sind an sechs Tagen pro Woche. Es gibt viele benachbarten Städte und Dörfer auf 10-20 Minuten, jeder mit seinem eigenen Markt und Fiestas.</de>
<fr>Duplex maison dans le village rural de Tibi, proche d’Alicante. La maison dispose de quatre chambres, chacune avec placards du sol au plafond, 3 salles de bains (maître en-suite), buanderie, cuisine séparée avec table à manger et grande derrière-cuisine, salon / salle à manger, grande terrasse donnant sur le parc, grande terrasse au dernier étage avec vue panoramique sur les montagnes et un parking souterrain avec stockage. Internet haut débit est disponible, ainsi qu'une connexion Wi-Fi qui est offré par la bibliothèque (2 minutes à pied). Tibi est un village calme, authentique, à environ 20 minutes de la côte. Tibi est un excellent choix pour les familles avec enfants ou pour les retraités qui veulent sortir de l'agitation de la côte ou la ville, mais avec toutes les commodités pour la vie moderne à proximité. Caché, mais pas isolé. Tibi a une nouvelle bibliothèque avec une connexion Wi-Fi, un nouveau marché intérieure, un nouveau centre médical et un nouveau centre sportif avec piscine. Tibi est populaire auprès des cyclistes et les promeneurs qui apprécient les nombreux sentiers de la région. Le parc national Maigmo se situe dans les limites de Tibi. Tibi est un endroit idéal pour explorer les villes et villages de la région. Le village est facilement accessible d’Alicante, l'aéroport d'Alicante et la côte. Au centre sportif local, vous pouvez jouer au tennis, le basket-ball, le handball de Valence et la natation. Le centre du village est familial et convivial avec le théâtre / cinéma en plein air, et des bars avec terrasses ombragées. Deux fois par semaine il y a un marché en plein air, et il y a aussi un nouveau marché intérieur. Les magasins sont ouverts six jours par semaine. Il y a beaucoup de villes et villages voisins de 10-20 minutes, chacune avec son propre marché et fiestas.</fr>
<nl>Duplex rijhuis in het landelijk dorp Tibi, bij Alicante. Het huis beschikt over 4 slaapkamers, elk met inbouwkasten van de vloer tot het plafond, 3 badkamers (master is en-suite), wasplaats, aparte keuken met eettafel en grote bijkeuken, woon- /eetkamer, groot terras met uitzicht op het park, groot terras op de bovenverdieping met weids uitzicht op de bergen, en een ondergrondse parkeergarage met opbergplaats. Breedband internet is beschikbaar, alsook gratis WiFi die de bibliotheek (op 2 minuten wandelafstand) u aanbiedt. Tibi is een rustig, authentiek dorp, ongeveer 20 minuten van de kust. Tibi is een uitstekende keuze voor gezinnen met kinderen of voor gepensioneerden die weg willen van de drukte van de kust of de stad, maar met alle faciliteiten voor het moderne leven dichtbij. Verborgen, maar niet geïsoleerd. Tibi heeft een nieuwe bibliotheek met gratis Wi-Fi, een nieuwe binnenmarkt, een nieuw medisch centrum en een nieuw sportcentrum met zwembad. Tibi is populair bij fietsers en wandelaars die genieten van de vele paden in de omgeving. Het Maigmo National Park ligt binnen de grenzen van Tibi. Tibi is een geweldige plek waaruit u de lokale steden en dorpen van het gebied kunt verkennen. Het dorp is goed bereikbaar vanuit Alicante, Alicante Airport en de kust. In het lokale sportcentrum kan u tennis spelen, basketbal, Valenciaanse handbal en zwemmen. Het dorpscentrum is gezinsvriendelijk met openlucht theater / bioscoop, en bars met schaduwrijke terrassen. Twee keer per week is er een buitenmarkt, en er is ook een nieuwe binnenmarkt. Winkels zijn 6 dagen per week open. Er zijn veel naburige steden en dorpen op 10-20 minuten rijden, met elk hun eigen markt en fiestas.</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/gJeYYddz95gvQ_Y5_mrOP1xT4U1xvTyn2ltdV1Gb7qINXYQL2Zwam2wAYODsQQMUkCr-ns7QrQFj3lp87w=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="2">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-3C-mgCtRI42dzcQH9NdKbCvSjwr6KgvHGV2DqFp6OIjrRcgXLXiQsFBgNGZwmysaMkC5Oq4lrSMj8HxEdU=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="3">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/gpKr-E8SrvB35AxNhGOsgyjf1ugbBuLNMzX8dCnBlLDKAdJCtKbk_bJ9uRw_CCUpBPjo0SMawgoXqMli=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="4">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/e9bwcSAIdvM0ZWIBMnVx8Rwb-fyvDE1yxyZ-0Fz3yuTAoiJQPjLnsIIA_EXmMD9Ujl9la47KOLMqwP1TqA=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="5">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/qznDEtIbnfzPEWetVYKKCsNsF-22XvLeU-4Zl1EfK2dfWsdvabjd4ibVBmYl7-FjAYSsxyqPZWhI9ztHXlM=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="6">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8cqrcFKAXwHVDj0dT7qRo46J1fGYn6nC6QBLyh5wHMewGUA_YdQOyfIqei2njmcMnPTPi0oN5HShanTsVg=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="7">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-oZnouNB1VrJDViReHU3MlwYJHPLcVQ4fCQRkhqxsab4wLlghZUfP7V7Dw-Tu2JhB4zDJHMoysS8pqoIpg=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="8">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/7NeM4votf-00QiOQKKdWteThw4gHQAWzZkf11xy5iUI6miuk4nGl_JuikZ673MYIG8q0AqlAZNnr1gSi1w=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="9">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/WSJX_NH-60IYqCrHlPAfoZdxAz_ZnlOCUZPnIEGb7tsgvYhAg1Zc8b2czkR9L1Plf8r3DhUaFC5tiULX=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="10">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/IXimltQAvqXqFgywODg_wUum3d2youEkCPAKe5LSREfBYA_DiCDFt9Yxq8Y-hvyVJTkfuXwXp3ectdlm=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="11">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/FBbnh702VnyMEvWLTUVqPHpkonF36fPPJwu4e3MinSdGaM4krJqlAceMLiyYdeR-Df2Rx7IV0DQOyjEV=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="12">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/XQDXn9P7aUYSO8aqGn0KcdqvYJRWLilGGRX01zfPATySlRhxOZ89L1W_LLzusKQsABKMwy8GqPQfJ7Bx3NY=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="13">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/72P5Nzeu5JG_4HyM2zP0kqEx-e6YC8iembKukdO04OAiiXPwJAYev6s64Cd7pXSsild2rSPj4zjtz17f3Ws=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="14">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/XAJe3SRlHiw1vW_UEH2z_2FJFTXjQHKuICQYwHXgZs9VJcGhgNpxoi1u4m_QR6mGNumWZcAspxaTmoaIXlc=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="15">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Apzm62h4SW7TjAx6hbJc767POKmGMF_QkZ2KBVNSkoxlOC5O7_VsgfkfGgXFY_nyMTbLP0KWMhYhVlR7FQ=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="16">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/0Zo88Ml4TIQsP35UcUoNBHZ3PDz7C5s5Dfhs87-fwiRwy9-wl7RSRFgVJ6TMWl-IiDz9-nTefOT-XU6-r4k=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="17">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/75DuulPu5YComplFD58fPXbfWnfQ6-VybjjgO7vHZktP2DbJ3igunKtkgkKK5b_AnkWSge-5E5Kqbv15Jbs=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="18">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/tNoIoVMgQ_Uad2Xz6nRouvROQpLQTf0BCITMa7W-jt0vNAIUt6Tt180-AHvV2OJFOI8SVhLD3N8VzYj4V4g=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="19">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/435e-VZQFMeaGF7RQvnirf7HBpdHMs_Ih2OI1frFkuah-AL4CeKz9i38YmpfWdHq2P8p_CHvzUUfggjUzGQ=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="20">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/s8fQ0XHx1n12BKpAiRa--UZ3WHy_jer3pq6QNmRn4fQhEoXt7f-5QIGhl7JbRJ2iuig7_9LcaFC9i5NXSg=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="21">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/DEqlQDwoSOoMVMTu-tF1K4wrElw2Zl7wngCdHEO-xwLP9gMrB93OiazR_dKNO2UxwIXwn2BK0bOs5k9D=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="22">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/W33WWyFiMq6AaFhwKjqts0UP8ScBunCJ13vB5HU4h3CdcBrfPfKUpdPp-EpxV_uFSrmLj5gRp2Xubyuj=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="23">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/OoX2YAKgbEsy1InwsMb_Izc1gaJpfkR-Qoz7fWYU3AT6RQv__AtaO6BozSyVwKz7v8WlDKjWA1gvPqv6=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="24">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/bXwxXRgFOfRnO74hBt-CiC-zgms6DCT7zwG5yfaq4rVmwkRp5CSd0EhPWGRX2QmOTgelInaOO9Mv7T7kxg=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="25">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/n4l2d_eh-C1h_xO1OdwaasUjwzFgHiP2Rzsa1CSANfouHaOsbCwPTWp0EfJaoO8ExDxjekmqQxzUvkIt=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="26">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/HXG6gCAR5F93RdysBBon4Av5z3_S0u0KT-WSjsxI-cN_jgAzBBlMry_99kj1QxPH1RoYgOvVPz7oCZR5Qw=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="27">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/L-p7lNqbOhlL64C6OQrtAmugEdnSJ_GVoiLuDBiXiEk9OFVc-RfMzEYUcV_ECN0ezDoIBunr9MkWu7F4ow=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="28">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/FkHPsQvhnXzYSURG3k-3acnbakcR-PM2om2rqWE4D0-yWiAiJBGZ6cC8CqimdfoBGvVs5V0_fEvL3V6MIqg=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="29">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/_dFhdOS7DWZQyFPEXIh4Cr9PZOalmHM9820_-MlCwh-ukaMVnQmT7fydBvEE3rpBXsvzYzVzpfhEYSez=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="30">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/N8I4JEP5hQIha34o87TK5kNQFkml3LyiIv7o_8O4zRLhnwxqJ-J1bvdL9n5eUJf6H2b2ANgNWSj2qjshFA=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="31">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/tr3dCEm5WuK_AI7JVIEi32fNz5qcHhFMvJ5Jmh0QTxrXhpjKheY6EWKUbAgoQ3kh2rLbgWON7Jg3dlKH3A=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="32">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/bIp8RId1RlnbumYj6HN9Dikh4c9a0ZyDFGjEaVPC3V10TZ8NNIbKLLdwa0wGeM51Y5bVbzlzLRoiSmXl=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="33">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/en9CSS6Y80xitPSUkt9LrDBo0HjQtrZ010YzzHqT-Ahkxv0SlQAbvg6vInARtkRIK4X8vPOTWl0k4PVPOjY=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="34">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ypC6EEgSjJ6o4t11PEdeOlvEBRRMLnGENx7Zg8_qgNMMErJr_e1bqLR79H9B6iMRPmI4QcOkDKD_kpFn=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="35">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/BApNEIwgv3pZf2tdfyAeJSM8IBe5o4-vz6ObBpq6tig08X3mhhye19Wjbs6CqHDndaXtPQVVBTjqnsjk=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="36">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/EoZWGpgW_U_UhulxGPT01rMyyk29ccXkzM7ZWQJVDn1Snj44VJ5oNXHqpV2AfjXj8XAEQGE5_2dx5mbu=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="37">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dSwhn3J0nnBYNBNTzMimIT80DXbmxYsG3FFi1kAIMnHEy2uiKN7moQVI5pLyv5mQSAUlSVmSd3f1Xovq-Q=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="38">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/YGDPC8y6OcPAsVmoJmiM5C6OXL5w-4w0SDfkdrFRwRE0cd1Pu8VdiAV1pNyalbs7D69tJlP3MYIH9fN8OA=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="39">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-64jusAEKz_Zv3hkFlZVSGgtlwdrxGjVHbES987EolA3H_X05qElLYdOfsUNHzkAUwet0h3vhzONHlzFbg=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="40">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/NXDUgBAauYyEAscp7kvTRaUpR-b0oyRo6vRkxdIp7oiNjq972IAxnCn0BwGRQcAFI2D_2x8akP7TUJm3=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="41">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/sMAp49OP4zpbEOHc_qyOG-qId_Uu4Y8jjjeLUgVWNLPDw8jvbNn1ktiyamf5L1OHuWErq84zBCu5YC5gKg=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="42">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1djh73uKMEqcYRvgm13n_UnWb7F4Hm-AGlz0ABXgfbkLEoZvboBwSGUQz7gPD2o4TIU0HT9_-co7Rxg8=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="43">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/KMvYr9jLFC4uS8dO8lrT3xF6FB0V7UXQwUdK9RAD0N7CdFW-m2IAl9FHG9C04XmkTG8c-PUtLYFPdUCsBGQ=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="44">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Apbw6wT9Y3Iq6o_tNFLhjNYZrM0d9aQFrcOpQx5zlkkjzAVoiiMRhiGShhaH1V_9-QsX8L8C3UN4izg-=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="45">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/voNvmkJMIWcy-FT40CzRL5HdC0THHX_ShPLsqVM0BLXnOGM3mFOaegYCRPaNiMv_gvchDQLX2iT6nj65dg=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="46">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/iOzDqvcGybsXxz_38x0hGhehG7hctqY11v8q4L5XAdJVVef114Wxi_sMpA-IyYu1mmzjZ7dH3ib4pB1s=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="47">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/QcdzpzbUIyF3qJtMvgCGzB4oS3lBuvt3vXkB63hMJpCzn0QZTZXQKJGMlnBMCUvpggbTL1GQr0DRAQXM5g=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="48">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1Fxz_QvKRBx9p6RXNN3qEZj6KrsA6EaClnFKdVE30oxfxGC8J2YsyVtNgnjI0ysR7QrF5hs6jyrML8E1UA=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="49">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/i1p1m1_Bgacu-m_c6zZEHgPLai1cIC1fpSLwmg2nOglMWeMbrYMQzQbjuf2pb-6GV9hlcVhbv3CKBFP4VQ=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="50">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/SQMVM7TyKSlW8P0CQRBVp3rq_R2pwYfziktV8hz_0j-BFqsi5GDKe7ZTl74Am3dILQjmpW1Y3i94NmIQ=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="51">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/gjaa-_47GPD3k3kqDCeBLiFf9pJm0_LIpqc21fvZN_HOmXbxHWluA6PeUI6FS-VEWzvvhltKMIqNYat0tA=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="52">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/707bi1FDiNGAkYA0LoRwqC4GGXoFPQHvXJnorLhTigvfxAx0m-GIxtcxOr4pmgrdosQcEHEvvSIAeMrI0Q=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
</root>
