<root>
<kyero>
<feed_version>2</feed_version>
</kyero>
<property>
<id>15070718</id>
<date>2018-07-03 11:21:18</date>
<ref>TH4-TB001DL</ref>
<price>219997</price>
<price_freq>sale</price_freq>
<type>
<en>Townhouse</en>
</type>
<town>Tibi</town>
<province>Alicante</province>
<location_detail>Tibi</location_detail>
<beds>4</beds>
<baths>3</baths>
<pool>0</pool>
<url>https://www.maxgoldhouse.com/4-bed-Townhouse-in-Tibi-1507.html</url>
<desc>
<en>Duplex Townhouse in authentic rural village (Tibi, Alicante). The house offers 4 bedrooms all with floor to ceiling built in wardrobes, 3 bathrooms (master is en-suite), internal laundry patio, large pantry, separate kitchen with dining table, lounge dining room, large entrance terrace overlooking the park, large upstairs balcony terrace with wide mountain views &amp; underground garage parking with store room.   Broadband Internet is available as well as the free Wi-Fi offered by the library 2 minutes walk away. Tibi is a quiet authentic living village community about 20 minutes inland from the coast up in the mountains.   Tibi is an excellent choice for families with children or for retired people who want to live away from the busy life of the coast or the city but with all the facilities for modern living close at hand. Hidden but not isolated, Tibi has a new library with free Wi-Fi, a new indoor market, a new medical centre and a new sports centre with swimming pool. Tibi is popular with cyclists and walkers who enjoy the many trails in the area. The Maigmo National Park is within Tibi's borders. Tibi is a great place from which you can explore the local towns and villages of the area. The village is well communicated with Alicante City, Alicante Airport &amp; the coast.. The village Sports Centre offers, tennis, five a side, basketball, Valencian hand ball court and swimming pool. The village centre is family friendly with outdoor theatre/cinema and bars with shady terraces. Outdoor market twice a week and new indoor market. Shops 6 days a week. There are many neighbouring towns and villages within 10-20 minutes away with market days &amp; fiestas. Wonderful place</en>
<de>Duplex-Reihenhaus in der ländlichen Gemeinde Tibi, in Alicante. Das Haus verfügt über vier Schlafzimmer, jeweils mit Einbauschränken vom Boden bis zur Decke, 3 Bäder (Master en-suite), Waschraum, separate Küche mit Esstisch und großem Hauswirtschaftsraum, Wohn- / Esszimmer, große Terrasse mit Blick auf den Park, große Terrasse auf der obersten Etage mit Panoramablick auf die Berge und eine Tiefgarage mit Abstellraum. Breitband-Internet ist verfügbar, sowie kostenloses WLAN, die Sie die Bibliothek bieten (2 Minuten zu Fuß). Tibi ist ein ruhiges, authentisches Dorf, etwa 20 Minuten von der Küste entfernt. Tibi ist eine ausgezeichnete Wahl für Familien mit Kindern oder für Rentner, die weg von der Hektik der Küste oder der Stadt bekommen wollen, aber mit allen Annehmlichkeiten für modernes Wohnen in der Nähe. Versteckt, aber nicht isoliert. Tibi hat eine neue Bibliothek mit kostenfreiem WLAN in einem neuen Markt, ein neues medizinisches Zentrum und ein neues Sportzentrum mit Schwimmbad. Tibi ist beliebt bei Radfahrern und Wanderer, die die vielen Wanderwege in der Umgebung. Der Maigmo Nationalpark liegt innerhalb der Grenzen von Tibi. Tibi ist ein großartiger Ort, um die lokalen Städte und Dörfer der Gegend zu erkunden. Das Dorf ist leicht von Alicante, Flughafen Alicante und der Küste. Das Sportcenter können Sie Tennis, Basketball, Handball und Schwimmen Valencia spielen. Das Dorfzentrum ist familienfreundlich mit Außen Theater / Kino sowie Bars mit schattigen Terrassen. Zweimal in der Woche gibt es einen Markt unter freiem Himmel, und es gibt auch eine neue Indoor-Markt. Die Geschäfte sind an sechs Tagen pro Woche. Es gibt viele benachbarten Städte und Dörfer auf 10-20 Minuten, jeder mit seinem eigenen Markt und Fiestas.</de>
<fr>Duplex maison dans le village rural de Tibi, proche d’Alicante. La maison dispose de quatre chambres, chacune avec placards du sol au plafond, 3 salles de bains (maître en-suite), buanderie, cuisine séparée avec table à manger et grande derrière-cuisine, salon / salle à manger, grande terrasse donnant sur le parc, grande terrasse au dernier étage avec vue panoramique sur les montagnes et un parking souterrain avec stockage. Internet haut débit est disponible, ainsi qu'une connexion Wi-Fi qui est offré par la bibliothèque (2 minutes à pied). Tibi est un village calme, authentique, à environ 20 minutes de la côte. Tibi est un excellent choix pour les familles avec enfants ou pour les retraités qui veulent sortir de l'agitation de la côte ou la ville, mais avec toutes les commodités pour la vie moderne à proximité. Caché, mais pas isolé. Tibi a une nouvelle bibliothèque avec une connexion Wi-Fi, un nouveau marché intérieure, un nouveau centre médical et un nouveau centre sportif avec piscine. Tibi est populaire auprès des cyclistes et les promeneurs qui apprécient les nombreux sentiers de la région. Le parc national Maigmo se situe dans les limites de Tibi. Tibi est un endroit idéal pour explorer les villes et villages de la région. Le village est facilement accessible d’Alicante, l'aéroport d'Alicante et la côte. Au centre sportif local, vous pouvez jouer au tennis, le basket-ball, le handball de Valence et la natation. Le centre du village est familial et convivial avec le théâtre / cinéma en plein air, et des bars avec terrasses ombragées. Deux fois par semaine il y a un marché en plein air, et il y a aussi un nouveau marché intérieur. Les magasins sont ouverts six jours par semaine. Il y a beaucoup de villes et villages voisins de 10-20 minutes, chacune avec son propre marché et fiestas.</fr>
<nl>Duplex rijhuis in het landelijk dorp Tibi, bij Alicante. Het huis beschikt over 4 slaapkamers, elk met inbouwkasten van de vloer tot het plafond, 3 badkamers (master is en-suite), wasplaats, aparte keuken met eettafel en grote bijkeuken, woon- /eetkamer, groot terras met uitzicht op het park, groot terras op de bovenverdieping met weids uitzicht op de bergen, en een ondergrondse parkeergarage met opbergplaats. Breedband internet is beschikbaar, alsook gratis WiFi die de bibliotheek (op 2 minuten wandelafstand) u aanbiedt. Tibi is een rustig, authentiek dorp, ongeveer 20 minuten van de kust. Tibi is een uitstekende keuze voor gezinnen met kinderen of voor gepensioneerden die weg willen van de drukte van de kust of de stad, maar met alle faciliteiten voor het moderne leven dichtbij. Verborgen, maar niet geïsoleerd. Tibi heeft een nieuwe bibliotheek met gratis Wi-Fi, een nieuwe binnenmarkt, een nieuw medisch centrum en een nieuw sportcentrum met zwembad. Tibi is populair bij fietsers en wandelaars die genieten van de vele paden in de omgeving. Het Maigmo National Park ligt binnen de grenzen van Tibi. Tibi is een geweldige plek waaruit u de lokale steden en dorpen van het gebied kunt verkennen. Het dorp is goed bereikbaar vanuit Alicante, Alicante Airport en de kust. In het lokale sportcentrum kan u tennis spelen, basketbal, Valenciaanse handbal en zwemmen. Het dorpscentrum is gezinsvriendelijk met openlucht theater / bioscoop, en bars met schaduwrijke terrassen. Twee keer per week is er een buitenmarkt, en er is ook een nieuwe binnenmarkt. Winkels zijn 6 dagen per week open. Er zijn veel naburige steden en dorpen op 10-20 minuten rijden, met elk hun eigen markt en fiestas.</nl>
</desc>
<images>
<image id="1">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/gJeYYddz95gvQ_Y5_mrOP1xT4U1xvTyn2ltdV1Gb7qINXYQL2Zwam2wAYODsQQMUkCr-ns7QrQFj3lp87w=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="2">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-3C-mgCtRI42dzcQH9NdKbCvSjwr6KgvHGV2DqFp6OIjrRcgXLXiQsFBgNGZwmysaMkC5Oq4lrSMj8HxEdU=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="3">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/gpKr-E8SrvB35AxNhGOsgyjf1ugbBuLNMzX8dCnBlLDKAdJCtKbk_bJ9uRw_CCUpBPjo0SMawgoXqMli=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="4">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/e9bwcSAIdvM0ZWIBMnVx8Rwb-fyvDE1yxyZ-0Fz3yuTAoiJQPjLnsIIA_EXmMD9Ujl9la47KOLMqwP1TqA=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="5">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/qznDEtIbnfzPEWetVYKKCsNsF-22XvLeU-4Zl1EfK2dfWsdvabjd4ibVBmYl7-FjAYSsxyqPZWhI9ztHXlM=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="6">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8cqrcFKAXwHVDj0dT7qRo46J1fGYn6nC6QBLyh5wHMewGUA_YdQOyfIqei2njmcMnPTPi0oN5HShanTsVg=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="7">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-oZnouNB1VrJDViReHU3MlwYJHPLcVQ4fCQRkhqxsab4wLlghZUfP7V7Dw-Tu2JhB4zDJHMoysS8pqoIpg=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="8">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/7NeM4votf-00QiOQKKdWteThw4gHQAWzZkf11xy5iUI6miuk4nGl_JuikZ673MYIG8q0AqlAZNnr1gSi1w=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="9">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/WSJX_NH-60IYqCrHlPAfoZdxAz_ZnlOCUZPnIEGb7tsgvYhAg1Zc8b2czkR9L1Plf8r3DhUaFC5tiULX=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="10">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/IXimltQAvqXqFgywODg_wUum3d2youEkCPAKe5LSREfBYA_DiCDFt9Yxq8Y-hvyVJTkfuXwXp3ectdlm=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="11">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/FBbnh702VnyMEvWLTUVqPHpkonF36fPPJwu4e3MinSdGaM4krJqlAceMLiyYdeR-Df2Rx7IV0DQOyjEV=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="12">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/XQDXn9P7aUYSO8aqGn0KcdqvYJRWLilGGRX01zfPATySlRhxOZ89L1W_LLzusKQsABKMwy8GqPQfJ7Bx3NY=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="13">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/72P5Nzeu5JG_4HyM2zP0kqEx-e6YC8iembKukdO04OAiiXPwJAYev6s64Cd7pXSsild2rSPj4zjtz17f3Ws=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="14">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/XAJe3SRlHiw1vW_UEH2z_2FJFTXjQHKuICQYwHXgZs9VJcGhgNpxoi1u4m_QR6mGNumWZcAspxaTmoaIXlc=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="15">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Apzm62h4SW7TjAx6hbJc767POKmGMF_QkZ2KBVNSkoxlOC5O7_VsgfkfGgXFY_nyMTbLP0KWMhYhVlR7FQ=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="16">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/0Zo88Ml4TIQsP35UcUoNBHZ3PDz7C5s5Dfhs87-fwiRwy9-wl7RSRFgVJ6TMWl-IiDz9-nTefOT-XU6-r4k=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="17">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/75DuulPu5YComplFD58fPXbfWnfQ6-VybjjgO7vHZktP2DbJ3igunKtkgkKK5b_AnkWSge-5E5Kqbv15Jbs=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="18">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/tNoIoVMgQ_Uad2Xz6nRouvROQpLQTf0BCITMa7W-jt0vNAIUt6Tt180-AHvV2OJFOI8SVhLD3N8VzYj4V4g=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="19">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/435e-VZQFMeaGF7RQvnirf7HBpdHMs_Ih2OI1frFkuah-AL4CeKz9i38YmpfWdHq2P8p_CHvzUUfggjUzGQ=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="20">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/s8fQ0XHx1n12BKpAiRa--UZ3WHy_jer3pq6QNmRn4fQhEoXt7f-5QIGhl7JbRJ2iuig7_9LcaFC9i5NXSg=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="21">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/DEqlQDwoSOoMVMTu-tF1K4wrElw2Zl7wngCdHEO-xwLP9gMrB93OiazR_dKNO2UxwIXwn2BK0bOs5k9D=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="22">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/W33WWyFiMq6AaFhwKjqts0UP8ScBunCJ13vB5HU4h3CdcBrfPfKUpdPp-EpxV_uFSrmLj5gRp2Xubyuj=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="23">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/OoX2YAKgbEsy1InwsMb_Izc1gaJpfkR-Qoz7fWYU3AT6RQv__AtaO6BozSyVwKz7v8WlDKjWA1gvPqv6=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="24">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/bXwxXRgFOfRnO74hBt-CiC-zgms6DCT7zwG5yfaq4rVmwkRp5CSd0EhPWGRX2QmOTgelInaOO9Mv7T7kxg=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="25">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/n4l2d_eh-C1h_xO1OdwaasUjwzFgHiP2Rzsa1CSANfouHaOsbCwPTWp0EfJaoO8ExDxjekmqQxzUvkIt=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="26">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/HXG6gCAR5F93RdysBBon4Av5z3_S0u0KT-WSjsxI-cN_jgAzBBlMry_99kj1QxPH1RoYgOvVPz7oCZR5Qw=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="27">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/L-p7lNqbOhlL64C6OQrtAmugEdnSJ_GVoiLuDBiXiEk9OFVc-RfMzEYUcV_ECN0ezDoIBunr9MkWu7F4ow=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="28">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/FkHPsQvhnXzYSURG3k-3acnbakcR-PM2om2rqWE4D0-yWiAiJBGZ6cC8CqimdfoBGvVs5V0_fEvL3V6MIqg=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="29">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/_dFhdOS7DWZQyFPEXIh4Cr9PZOalmHM9820_-MlCwh-ukaMVnQmT7fydBvEE3rpBXsvzYzVzpfhEYSez=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="30">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/N8I4JEP5hQIha34o87TK5kNQFkml3LyiIv7o_8O4zRLhnwxqJ-J1bvdL9n5eUJf6H2b2ANgNWSj2qjshFA=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="31">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/tr3dCEm5WuK_AI7JVIEi32fNz5qcHhFMvJ5Jmh0QTxrXhpjKheY6EWKUbAgoQ3kh2rLbgWON7Jg3dlKH3A=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="32">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/bIp8RId1RlnbumYj6HN9Dikh4c9a0ZyDFGjEaVPC3V10TZ8NNIbKLLdwa0wGeM51Y5bVbzlzLRoiSmXl=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="33">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/en9CSS6Y80xitPSUkt9LrDBo0HjQtrZ010YzzHqT-Ahkxv0SlQAbvg6vInARtkRIK4X8vPOTWl0k4PVPOjY=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="34">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/ypC6EEgSjJ6o4t11PEdeOlvEBRRMLnGENx7Zg8_qgNMMErJr_e1bqLR79H9B6iMRPmI4QcOkDKD_kpFn=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="35">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/BApNEIwgv3pZf2tdfyAeJSM8IBe5o4-vz6ObBpq6tig08X3mhhye19Wjbs6CqHDndaXtPQVVBTjqnsjk=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="36">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/EoZWGpgW_U_UhulxGPT01rMyyk29ccXkzM7ZWQJVDn1Snj44VJ5oNXHqpV2AfjXj8XAEQGE5_2dx5mbu=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="37">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/dSwhn3J0nnBYNBNTzMimIT80DXbmxYsG3FFi1kAIMnHEy2uiKN7moQVI5pLyv5mQSAUlSVmSd3f1Xovq-Q=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="38">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/YGDPC8y6OcPAsVmoJmiM5C6OXL5w-4w0SDfkdrFRwRE0cd1Pu8VdiAV1pNyalbs7D69tJlP3MYIH9fN8OA=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="39">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-64jusAEKz_Zv3hkFlZVSGgtlwdrxGjVHbES987EolA3H_X05qElLYdOfsUNHzkAUwet0h3vhzONHlzFbg=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="40">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/NXDUgBAauYyEAscp7kvTRaUpR-b0oyRo6vRkxdIp7oiNjq972IAxnCn0BwGRQcAFI2D_2x8akP7TUJm3=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="41">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/sMAp49OP4zpbEOHc_qyOG-qId_Uu4Y8jjjeLUgVWNLPDw8jvbNn1ktiyamf5L1OHuWErq84zBCu5YC5gKg=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="42">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1djh73uKMEqcYRvgm13n_UnWb7F4Hm-AGlz0ABXgfbkLEoZvboBwSGUQz7gPD2o4TIU0HT9_-co7Rxg8=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="43">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/KMvYr9jLFC4uS8dO8lrT3xF6FB0V7UXQwUdK9RAD0N7CdFW-m2IAl9FHG9C04XmkTG8c-PUtLYFPdUCsBGQ=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="44">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Apbw6wT9Y3Iq6o_tNFLhjNYZrM0d9aQFrcOpQx5zlkkjzAVoiiMRhiGShhaH1V_9-QsX8L8C3UN4izg-=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="45">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/voNvmkJMIWcy-FT40CzRL5HdC0THHX_ShPLsqVM0BLXnOGM3mFOaegYCRPaNiMv_gvchDQLX2iT6nj65dg=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="46">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/iOzDqvcGybsXxz_38x0hGhehG7hctqY11v8q4L5XAdJVVef114Wxi_sMpA-IyYu1mmzjZ7dH3ib4pB1s=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="47">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/QcdzpzbUIyF3qJtMvgCGzB4oS3lBuvt3vXkB63hMJpCzn0QZTZXQKJGMlnBMCUvpggbTL1GQr0DRAQXM5g=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="48">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1Fxz_QvKRBx9p6RXNN3qEZj6KrsA6EaClnFKdVE30oxfxGC8J2YsyVtNgnjI0ysR7QrF5hs6jyrML8E1UA=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="49">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/i1p1m1_Bgacu-m_c6zZEHgPLai1cIC1fpSLwmg2nOglMWeMbrYMQzQbjuf2pb-6GV9hlcVhbv3CKBFP4VQ=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="50">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/SQMVM7TyKSlW8P0CQRBVp3rq_R2pwYfziktV8hz_0j-BFqsi5GDKe7ZTl74Am3dILQjmpW1Y3i94NmIQ=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="51">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/gjaa-_47GPD3k3kqDCeBLiFf9pJm0_LIpqc21fvZN_HOmXbxHWluA6PeUI6FS-VEWzvvhltKMIqNYat0tA=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image><image id="52">
<url>http://lh3.googleusercontent.com/707bi1FDiNGAkYA0LoRwqC4GGXoFPQHvXJnorLhTigvfxAx0m-GIxtcxOr4pmgrdosQcEHEvvSIAeMrI0Q=s0-rj-e30-v2?.jpg</url>
</image>
</images>
</property>
</root>
